{"classes":["ACT","FAC","PERSON","GPE","LOC","TIME","DATE","ORG","NORP","EVENT","WORK_OF_ART","PRODUCT","GPE_WHO","LOC_WHO","FAC_WHO"],"annotations":[["#BREAKING: Nightmare in #Itaewon, Dozens of SouthKorean #Halloween revellers treated for cardiac arrest on pavement after stampede in Itaewon Around 160 people dead &amp; 100+ injured in a stampede during Halloween celebrations\r",{"entities":[[25,32,"FAC"],[44,55,"PERSON"],[57,66,"DATE"],[77,84,"ACT"],[134,141,"FAC"],[176,183,"ACT"],[205,214,"DATE"]]}],["storm system moving through the South will bring threats of severe thunderstorms and flooding rainfall through Saturday before weakening as it moves into the Ohio Valley around Halloween. The Storm Prediction Center issued a Tornado Watch\r",{"entities":[[13,19,"ACT"],[32,37,"LOC"],[43,48,"ACT"],[85,93,"ACT"],[111,119,"DATE"],[143,148,"ACT"],[158,169,"LOC"],[177,187,"DATE"],[192,215,"ORG"]]}],["\"DePape said that he was looking for Nancy Pelosi because he wanted to take her hostage and effectively interrogate her.\"\r",{"entities":[[1,7,"PERSON"],[8,12,"ACT"],[25,32,"ACT"],[37,49,"PERSON"],[61,67,"ACT"],[71,75,"ACT"],[104,115,"ACT"]]}],["\"In a nightshirt, Pelosi then told the assailant he had to use the restroom\" What is this, the 1800's? What man wears a nite shirt anymore?\r",{"entities":[[18,24,"PERSON"],[30,34,"ACT"],[59,62,"ACT"],[95,99,"DATE"],[112,117,"ACT"]]}],["\"LIVE: Presidential Summit on Gender-Based Violence and Femicide - SABC News - Breaking news, special reports, world, business, sport coverage of all South African current events. Africa's news leader.\"\r",{"entities":[[7,19,"PERSON"],[20,26,"ACT"],[150,163,"NORP"]]}],["\"More than half the fatalities were from a series of flash floods and landslides that destroyed villages on the Philippines' southern island of Mindanao over the weekend, the nation’s disaster agency said.\" #ClimateEmergency\r",{"entities":[[86,95,"ACT"],[112,123,"GPE"],[144,152,"GPE"],[158,169,"DATE"],[200,205,"ACT"]]}],["\"Safety Measures Ignored In Hurry To Open (Bridge)\": Engineer On Gujarat Tragedy - NDTV\r",{"entities":[[17,24,"ACT"],[37,41,"ACT"],[65,72,"GPE"],[83,87,"ORG"]]}],["\"Spoiler Alert\" HawaiiNewsNow Earthquake activities on Hawaii island in the week. It is likely that either a volcanic eruption or a large earthquake may occur in the near future. be cautious. #BREAKING\r",{"entities":[[55,61,"GPE"],[72,81,"DATE"],[153,158,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING Death toll from #Philippines flash floods rises to 67: official tally\r",{"entities":[[27,38,"GPE"],[52,57,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING Officials in Seoul said that at least 150 people were dead and 100 others were injured after a stampede in the South Korean capital's popular Itaewon district, where crowds had gathered to celebrate Halloween. newstakofficial\r",{"entities":[[23,28,"GPE"],[29,33,"ACT"],[89,96,"ACT"],[121,133,"NORP"],[152,159,"FAC"],[187,195,"ACT"],[199,208,"ACT"],[209,219,"DATE"],[220,235,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING Philippine floods death toll rises to 31: official (AFP)\r",{"entities":[[10,20,"NORP"],[39,44,"ACT"],[62,65,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING The STC President offers condolences to the President of #India for the victims of the collapse of the pedestrian suspension bridge in India's western state of Gujarat #south24\r",{"entities":[[14,17,"ORG"],[28,34,"ACT"],[68,73,"GPE"],[97,105,"ACT"],[145,150,"GPE"],[170,177,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING Death toll from Philippines flash floods rises to 67: official tally #AFP\r",{"entities":[[26,37,"GPE"],[51,56,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING On Friday, Nancy Pelosi was the target of an assassination attempt by a MAGA cultist. If she had been at home, she would be dead. The Speaker of the House would have been killed in an act of extremist political violence that severely injured her husband. Please RT\r",{"entities":[[13,19,"DATE"],[21,33,"PERSON"],[82,86,"ORG"],[181,187,"ACT"],[244,251,"ACT"],[272,274,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING score for October is in - they beat #NYC once again, with monthly stats: 309 shot, and 64 dead. #crime\r",{"entities":[[20,27,"DATE"],[41,45,"ACT"],[47,50,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING Following Morbi tragedy, PM Modi cancels road show, page committee conference in Gujarat ... Afterall AntiNational Elements Are Successful in Stopping Modi's Rally in Election Bound Gujarat...\r",{"entities":[[38,42,"PERSON"],[43,50,"ACT"],[91,98,"GPE"],[152,160,"ACT"],[161,165,"PERSON"],[192,199,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING A 5.9 magnitude earthquake hits Peru\r",{"entities":[[37,41,"ACT"],[42,46,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING 'Massive attack' by Russia on Ukraine energy facilities: Ukraine presidency\r",{"entities":[[19,25,"ACT"],[30,36,"GPE"],[40,47,"GPE"],[67,74,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING - Potential Tropical Cyclone 15 forms in Caribbean Sea - situated 265 miles SE of Kingston Tropical Storm Watches issued for Jamaica &amp; Grand Cayman\r",{"entities":[[51,64,"LOC"],[67,75,"ACT"],[92,123,"EVENT"],[124,130,"ACT"],[135,142,"GPE"],[149,161,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING 100 Killed as 150 years old Gujarat Bridge Collapses Week After Renovation. Hope the Rescue and relief efforts save the missing and treat the injured. Praying for the families, rescue teams, relief work and the government! #gurajatbridge\r",{"entities":[[14,20,"ACT"],[24,33,"DATE"],[38,45,"GPE"],[53,62,"ACT"],[63,67,"DATE"],[86,90,"ACT"],[121,125,"ACT"],[142,147,"ACT"],[161,168,"ACT"],[187,193,"ACT"],[208,212,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING : #MorbiBridgeCollapse | Prime Minister Narendra Modi to visit Morbi, Gujarat tomorrow, 1st November. #PMModi\r",{"entities":[[50,63,"PERSON"],[67,72,"ACT"],[73,78,"PERSON"],[80,87,"GPE"],[88,96,"DATE"],[98,111,"DATE"]]}],["#BREAKING : At least 60 people have died after a suspension bridge collapsed in India's Gujarat state, an official says. #news\r",{"entities":[[36,40,"ACT"],[67,76,"ACT"],[80,85,"GPE"],[88,95,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING A Bridge has collapsed in India's Gujarat state sending hundreds plunging into a river, with at least 32 people confirmed dead.\r",{"entities":[[23,32,"ACT"],[36,41,"GPE"],[44,51,"GPE"],[58,65,"ACT"],[122,131,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING An HPD SGT.says the rap group Migos, specifically Quavo &amp; Takeoff were at Billiards &amp; bowling alley on San Jacinto., when the shooting happened just before 3 a.m. A man police say was shot in the head &amp; killed.Investigators won’t confirm if it was a group member KHOU\r",{"entities":[[60,65,"PERSON"],[121,133,"GPE"],[153,161,"ACT"],[174,180,"TIME"],[194,197,"ACT"],[202,206,"ACT"],[252,259,"ACT"],[285,289,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING At least 100 people are feared trapped after a #cablebridge collapsed in #India's Gujarat province, on Sunday evening, local media NDTV reported.\r",{"entities":[[34,40,"ACT"],[41,48,"ACT"],[70,79,"ACT"],[84,89,"GPE"],[92,99,"GPE"],[113,119,"DATE"],[120,127,"TIME"],[141,145,"ORG"],[146,154,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING At least 130 people were killed and 100 others were injured in a stampede in the popular Itaewon neighbourhood of the South Korean capital, where crowds had come to celebrate Halloween. #SeoulStampede\r",{"entities":[[35,41,"ACT"],[62,69,"ACT"],[99,106,"FAC"],[128,140,"NORP"],[167,171,"ACT"],[175,184,"ACT"],[185,195,"DATE"]]}],["#BREAKING At least 149 people were killed, 76 others injured in a deadly stampede in Seoul's Itaewon district, as huge crowds of partygoers stampeded at late-night Halloween celebrations, fire authorities said Sunday. For more:\r",{"entities":[[35,41,"ACT"],[53,60,"ACT"],[85,90,"GPE"],[93,100,"FAC"],[140,149,"ACT"],[153,163,"TIME"],[164,173,"DATE"],[205,209,"ACT"],[210,217,"DATE"]]}],["#BREAKING At least 30 people were killed and dozens critically injured when a suspension bridge in India's western Gujarat state collapsed on Sunday, Indian government said.\r",{"entities":[[34,40,"ACT"],[63,70,"ACT"],[99,104,"GPE"],[107,122,"LOC"],[129,138,"ACT"],[142,148,"DATE"],[150,156,"NORP"],[168,172,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING At least 59 people have been killed and 150 others injured in a stampede in Seoul's Itaewon district amid Halloween festivities, the Yonhap news agency reports.\r",{"entities":[[39,45,"ACT"],[61,68,"ACT"],[86,91,"GPE"],[94,101,"FAC"],[116,125,"DATE"],[143,161,"ORG"],[162,169,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING At least 60 dead in suspension bridge collapse in India’s Gujarat state.",{"entities":[[22,26,"ACT"],[48,56,"ACT"],[68,75,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING At least 60 dead in suspension bridge collapse in India’s Gujarat state.",{"entities":[[22,26,"ACT"],[48,56,"ACT"],[68,75,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING Climate Activists Storm BlackRock HQ in NYC with pitchforks, dump coal on escalator as one man tries to stop and block them . Video by Ken Lopez / FreedomNTV\r",{"entities":[[34,43,"ORG"],[50,53,"GPE"],[71,75,"ACT"],[105,110,"ACT"],[114,118,"ACT"],[123,128,"ACT"],[145,154,"PERSON"]]}],["#BREAKING Death toll from Philippines flash floods rises to 67: official tally\r",{"entities":[[26,37,"GPE"],[51,56,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING Death toll from Philippines flash floods rises to 67: official tally #Philippines\r",{"entities":[[26,37,"GPE"],[51,56,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING MOSCOW (UrduPoint News / Sputnik - 31st October, 2022) Russia has sent representatives ...\r",{"entities":[[10,16,"GPE"],[18,32,"ORG"],[35,42,"ORG"],[45,63,"DATE"],[65,71,"GPE_WHO"],[76,80,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING News: About 150 people reported hurt in stampede in South Korea Emergency officials received at least 81 calls from people in the Itaewon area saying they were having difficulty breathing . #stampede\r",{"entities":[[33,41,"ACT"],[42,46,"ACT"],[62,73,"GPE"],[94,102,"ACT"],[140,147,"GPE"],[153,159,"ACT"],[170,176,"ACT"],[188,197,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING Philippine floods death toll rises to 31: official\r",{"entities":[[10,20,"NORP"],[39,44,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING Protest at the Morbi bridge collapse site ahead of Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s arrival . This is Gujarat Opposition politician Reshma Patel . She says families of victims in this tragedy need answers about what’s happened .\r",{"entities":[[21,37,"FAC"],[38,46,"ACT"],[76,91,"PERSON"],[110,117,"GPE"],[140,152,"PERSON"],[159,163,"ACT"],[200,204,"ACT"],[226,234,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING Rapper Takeoff, member of Migos, shot dead at 28: TMZ website\r",{"entities":[[36,41,"ORG"],[43,47,"ACT"],[60,63,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING Rapper Takeoff, of the group Migos, has been shot and killed . He was 28.\r",{"entities":[[39,44,"ORG"],[55,59,"ACT"],[64,70,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING Russia says hit Ukraine energy infrastructure with 'high-precision' strikes\r",{"entities":[[10,16,"GPE_WHO"],[17,21,"ACT"],[22,25,"ACT"],[26,33,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING Russian defence ministry says it wants 'commitments' from Ukraine not to use grain exports corridor for military purposes\r",{"entities":[[10,34,"ORG"],[35,39,"ACT"],[43,48,"ACT"],[49,61,"ACT"],[68,75,"GPE"],[83,86,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING The Kremlin on Tuesday accused the United Kingdom of \"directing and coordinating\" explosions on the Nord Stream gas pipelines .\r",{"entities":[[25,32,"DATE"],[33,40,"ACT"],[41,59,"GPE"],[64,73,"ACT"],[78,90,"ACT"],[110,121,"FAC"]]}],["#BREAKING The Storm has arrived in #Europe\r",{"entities":[[24,31,"ACT"],[36,42,"LOC"]]}],["#BREAKING The head of Naftogaz of Ukraine Yuri Vitrenko wrote his resignation .\r",{"entities":[[22,30,"ORG"],[42,55,"PERSON"],[56,61,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING UPDATE The death toll from the crowd crush in Seoul’s Itaewon nightlife area has risen to 151, the city fire department said Sunday . Among the dead are 19 foreign nationals . Eighty-two others have been injured . -CNN\r",{"entities":[[56,63,"GPE"],[64,71,"GPE"],[91,96,"ACT"],[130,134,"GPE"],[135,141,"DATE"],[214,221,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING Ukraine says targeted by 'more than 50 missiles' from Russia\r",{"entities":[[10,17,"GPE_WHO"],[18,22,"ACT"],[23,31,"ACT"],[64,70,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING Very sad scene . Over 100 people experience cardiac arrest for over crowding in Itaewon where thousands gathered for Halloween . #CardiacArrest\r",{"entities":[[43,53,"ACT"],[90,97,"GPE"],[114,122,"ACT"],[127,136,"DATE"]]}],["#BREAKING on #MorbiBridgeScam | Republic questions Gujarat CM Bhupendra Patel on the Morbi Bridge disaster: Why aren't specific people named in the FIR? Why was the bridge allowed to open despite no fitness clearance? Tune in #LIVE -\r",{"entities":[[14,29,"EVENT"],[41,50,"ACT"],[51,58,"GPE"],[62,77,"PERSON"],[81,97,"FAC"],[135,140,"ACT"],[172,179,"ACT"],[183,187,"ACT"],[218,222,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING on #MorbiBridgeScam | Republic questions Gujarat CM Bhupendra Patel on the Morbi Bridge disaster; Tune in #LIVE -\r",{"entities":[[14,29,"EVENT"],[41,50,"ACT"],[51,61,"GPE"],[62,77,"PERSON"],[81,97,"FAC"],[108,112,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | 'Government 's priority to rescue the stranded people . Death toll is 132,' says Gujarat Home Minister on Morbi bridge collapse . Tune in #LIVE:\r",{"entities":[[39,45,"ACT"],[50,58,"ACT"],[88,92,"ACT"],[93,100,"GPE"],[118,130,"FAC"],[142,146,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | 132 deaths have been reported so far: Gujarat Home Minister Harsh Sanghavi on #MorbiBridgeCollapse\r",{"entities":[[33,41,"ACT"],[50,57,"GPE"],[72,86,"PERSON"]]}],["#BREAKING | 2 staff members of Oreva Group arrested by Gujarat Police on the basis of an FIR filed in the #GujaratBridgeCollapse:\r",{"entities":[[31,42,"ORG"],[43,51,"ACT"],[55,62,"GPE"],[93,98,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | AIMIM chief Asaduddin Owaisi wades into UCC debate after Gujarat govt 's big announcement . Tune in -\r",{"entities":[[12,17,"ORG"],[24,40,"PERSON"],[41,46,"ACT"],[52,55,"ORG"],[69,76,"GPE"],[104,108,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Big Move: Gujarat govt likely to formulate Uniform Civil Code (UCC) panel today, say sources . Tune in here for more -\r",{"entities":[[22,29,"GPE"],[45,54,"ACT"],[86,91,"DATE"],[93,96,"ACT"],[107,111,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Big claim by Gujarat minister Harsh Sanghavi . The leader accuses AAP of 'sending money through hawala route' to Gujarat ahead of the polls . Tune in #LIVE:\r",{"entities":[[25,32,"GPE"],[42,56,"PERSON"],[70,77,"ACT"],[78,81,"ORG"],[85,93,"ACT"],[125,132,"GPE"],[154,158,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Death count in Gujarat bridge collapse climbs to 130, 177 rescued so far\r",{"entities":[[27,41,"FAC"],[42,50,"ACT"],[51,57,"ACT"],[70,77,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Delhi CM Arvind Kejriwal backs UCC but questions Gujarat govt 's intention; asks to 'bring all communities together' -\r",{"entities":[[12,17,"GPE"],[21,36,"PERSON"],[37,42,"ACT"],[43,46,"ORG"],[51,60,"ACT"],[61,73,"ORG"],[88,92,"ACT"],[96,102,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Gujarat Chief Minister Bhupendra Patel reaches the #MorbiBridgeCollapse site; Tune in #LIVE here:\r",{"entities":[[12,19,"GPE"],[35,50,"PERSON"],[51,58,"ACT"],[90,94,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Gujarat Home Minister Harsh Sanghavi tells Republic he will update on the latest casualty figures shortly; Tune in #LIVE here -\r",{"entities":[[12,19,"GPE"],[34,48,"PERSON"],[49,54,"ACT"],[72,78,"ACT"],[119,123,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Gujarat Home Minister addresses media about the Morbi bridge collapse and shares details of the rescue operations . Tune in #LIVE:\r",{"entities":[[12,19,"GPE"],[34,43,"ACT"],[56,72,"FAC"],[73,81,"ACT"],[86,92,"ACT"],[128,132,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Gujarat Home Minister assures 'rescue operations in full swing' as cable bridge collapse leaves several dead . Tune in -\r",{"entities":[[12,19,"GPE"],[34,41,"ACT"],[92,100,"ACT"],[101,107,"ACT"],[123,127,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Gujarat Morbi Bridge Accident - More than 100 dead so far; 177 people have been rescued . Army, Air Force, Navy in rescue operation - State Information Department\r",{"entities":[[12,19,"GPE"],[20,32,"FAC"],[92,99,"ACT"],[146,174,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING | In a massive claim, Gujarat Minister Harsh Sanghavi accuses AAP of 'sending money through hawala route' ahead of assembly elections -\r",{"entities":[[32,39,"GPE"],[49,63,"PERSON"],[64,71,"ACT"],[72,75,"ORG"],[79,87,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Morbi suspension bridge accident in Gujarat - death toll rises to 91 | #MorbiBridgeCollapse | #Gujarat\r",{"entities":[[12,35,"FAC"],[48,55,"GPE"],[58,63,"ACT"],[107,114,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING | Morbi suspension bridge accident in Gujarat - death toll rises to 91 | #MorbiBridgeCollapse | #Gujarat\r",{"entities":[[12,35,"FAC"],[48,55,"GPE"],[69,74,"ACT"],[107,114,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING | Most Halloween festivals, events &amp; parades cancelled in South Korea as the country mourns the deaths of 151 people in an overnight stampede in Seoul 's Itaewon last night: Local reports -\r",{"entities":[[17,26,"DATE"],[59,68,"ACT"],[72,83,"GPE"],[99,105,"ACT"],[137,146,"TIME"],[159,164,"GPE"],[168,175,"GPE"],[176,186,"TIME"]]}],["#BREAKING | Multiple agencies, assisted by local residents, continue rescue operations in the Machchhu river in Gujarat as Republic reports from the ticket counter of Morbi Bridge . Tune in #LIVE here:\r",{"entities":[[31,39,"ACT"],[60,68,"ACT"],[69,75,"ACT"],[94,102,"GPE"],[112,119,"GPE"],[167,179,"FAC"],[182,186,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | On Gujarat bridge collapse, Supreme Court to hear petition on November 14 seeking judicial probe\r",{"entities":[[15,29,"FAC"],[30,38,"ACT"],[40,53,"ORG"],[57,61,"ACT"],[74,85,"DATE"]]}],["#BREAKING | Outrage against human rights abuse in China . 50 nations seek release of detained Uyghurs . Tune in #LIVE:\r",{"entities":[[50,55,"GPE"],[69,73,"ACT"],[85,93,"ACT"],[94,101,"WORK_OF_ART"],[104,108,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | PM Modi visits site of Gujarat bridge collapse in which 135 died on Sunday\r",{"entities":[[15,19,"PERSON"],[20,26,"ACT"],[35,49,"FAC"],[50,58,"ACT"],[72,76,"ACT"],[80,86,"DATE"]]}],["#BREAKING | PM Narendra Modi cancels his events in Gujarat today after 132 die in bridge tragedy\r",{"entities":[[15,28,"PERSON"],[29,36,"ACT"],[51,58,"GPE"],[59,64,"DATE"],[75,78,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | PM Narendra Modi cancels his events in Gujarat today after 132 die in bridge tragedy NDTV 's Sanket Upadhyay reports\r",{"entities":[[15,28,"PERSON"],[29,36,"ACT"],[51,58,"GPE"],[59,64,"DATE"],[75,78,"ACT"],[97,101,"ORG"],[105,120,"PERSON"],[121,128,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING | Republic impact: Gujarat police places focus on Oreva, seeks details from registrar of companies . Tune in -\r",{"entities":[[29,36,"GPE"],[51,56,"ACT"],[67,72,"GPE"],[111,115,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING 1/ San Francisco District Attorney BrookeJenkinsSF releases new details about attack on Speaker Nancy Pelosi 's husband, Paul Pelosi . She says David Depape broke a glass door to get into the Pelosi 's SF home, went to 2nd floor to find Paul Pelosi sleeping in bed .\r",{"entities":[[13,26,"GPE"],[45,60,"PERSON"],[61,69,"ACT"],[106,118,"PERSON"],[131,142,"PERSON"],[149,153,"ACT"],[154,166,"PERSON"],[167,172,"ACT"],[189,192,"ACT"],[202,208,"PERSON"],[212,214,"GPE"],[221,225,"ACT"],[242,246,"ACT"],[247,258,"PERSON"],[259,267,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: is in trouble said thousands of people have breathing problems after the #stampede at Itaewon in #Seoul,\r",{"entities":[[25,29,"ACT"],[55,64,"ACT"],[97,104,"GPE"],[109,114,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING: fire department said 81 people have breathing problems after the #stampede at Itaewon in #Seoul, South Korea Saturday night when over 100 thousand revellers crammed into the place for #Halloween celebrations . #SeoulStampede\r",{"entities":[[27,31,"ACT"],[47,56,"ACT"],[89,96,"GPE"],[101,106,"GPE"],[108,119,"GPE"],[120,128,"DATE"],[129,134,"TIME"],[168,175,"ACT"],[196,218,"EVENT"]]}],["#BREAKING: fire department said more than 1000 people have breathing problems after the #stampede at Itaewon in #Seoul, when over 100 thousand revellers crammed into the place for #Halloween celebrations . Follow my account for more updates #stampede\r",{"entities":[[27,31,"ACT"],[59,68,"ACT"],[101,108,"GPE"],[113,118,"GPE"],[153,160,"ACT"],[181,203,"EVENT"],[206,212,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: Suspension Bridge in BJP’s Gujarat collapsed . More than 400 people fell into water and got injured! To be noted that, this bridge was renovated &amp; opened just 5 days ago . This is Gujarat’s development\r",{"entities":[[32,37,"ORG"],[38,45,"GPE"],[46,55,"ACT"],[79,83,"ACT"],[103,110,"ACT"],[118,123,"ACT"],[146,155,"ACT"],[162,168,"ACT"],[174,184,"DATE"],[195,204,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING: 22 foreigners killed in Itaewon disaster, South Korean fire officials say; at least four Chinese and four Iranian citizens among those dead - Yonhap\r",{"entities":[[25,31,"ACT"],[35,42,"FAC"],[53,65,"NORP"],[81,84,"ACT"],[100,107,"NORP"],[117,124,"NORP"],[153,159,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING: CNN reports #Iran is sending 1,000 pieces of weaponry to #Russia for use in #Ukraine, including surface-to-surface missiles .\r",{"entities":[[11,14,"ORG"],[15,22,"ACT"],[24,28,"GPE_WHO"],[32,45,"ACT"],[69,75,"GPE"],[88,95,"GPE"],[97,106,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: At least 59 people killed, 150 others injured in stampede incident in Itaewon area of Seoul, South Korea - Yonhap\r",{"entities":[[30,36,"ACT"],[49,56,"ACT"],[81,88,"GPE"],[97,102,"GPE"],[104,115,"GPE"],[118,124,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING: Bridge with up to 400 people partially collapses into river in western India 's Gujarat\r",{"entities":[[50,59,"ACT"],[82,87,"GPE"],[91,98,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING: Death toll from Itaewon disaster rises to 154, including 26 foreigners; 33 people remain in critical condition - Yonhap\r",{"entities":[[27,34,"GPE"],[44,49,"ACT"],[58,67,"ACT"],[93,99,"ACT"],[124,130,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING: Death toll from Morbi bridge disaster in western India 's Gujarat reaches 132 - ANI Gujarat | Early morning visuals from the accident site in #Morbi where more than 100 people have lost their lives after a cable bridge collapsed . Gujarat Home Minister Harsh Sanghavi is also present at the spot .\r",{"entities":[[27,39,"FAC"],[60,65,"GPE"],[69,76,"GPE"],[77,84,"ACT"],[105,118,"TIME"],[154,159,"GPE"],[192,196,"ACT"],[230,239,"ACT"],[242,249,"GPE"],[264,278,"PERSON"],[287,294,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: Death toll from Philippine flash floods rises to 67\r",{"entities":[[27,37,"NORP"],[51,56,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: Fantastic #Maddow—Why is Steve Bannon asking #Bolsonaro, who has lately been courting top military officials, not to leave office? Simple answer, Maddow: #Fascism\r",{"entities":[[22,32,"PERSON"],[36,48,"PERSON"],[49,55,"ACT"],[57,66,"PERSON"],[88,96,"ACT"],[128,133,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: Itaewon stampede death toll rises to 153, South Korean authorities say - Yonhap\r",{"entities":[[11,18,"GPE"],[39,44,"ACT"],[53,65,"NORP"],[78,81,"ACT"],[84,90,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING: MAGA Trump Republican Qunt Supporter of Mostly White Extremist Christian Domestic Terrorism, #Arizona Kari Lake, made the distasteful joke days after Paul Pelosi was brutally attacked with a hammer during a home invasion . via HuffPostPol\r",{"entities":[[22,32,"NORP"],[33,37,"PERSON"],[74,83,"NORP"],[105,112,"GPE"],[124,128,"ACT"],[150,160,"DATE"],[161,172,"PERSON"],[186,194,"ACT"],[238,249,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING: Migos rapper Takeoff has died, according to TMZ . The 28 year old rapper was reportedly shot at a bowling alley in Houston where he and rapper Quavo were playing dice early this morning . : Getty\r",{"entities":[[11,16,"ORG"],[36,40,"ACT"],[42,51,"ACT"],[55,58,"ORG"],[65,76,"DATE"],[99,103,"ACT"],[126,133,"GPE"],[154,159,"PERSON"],[165,172,"ACT"],[178,196,"TIME"],[201,206,"ORG"]]}],["#BREAKING: Minor M2.1 earthquake recorded in south Las Vegas valley . -USGS",{"entities":[[33,41,"ACT"],[51,67,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING: Pelosi suspect charged and wanted to hold House Speaker hostage, feds say\r",{"entities":[[11,17,"PERSON"],[26,33,"ACT"],[38,44,"ACT"],[48,52,"ACT"],[81,84,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: Rapper Takeoff, one-third of the hip-hop group Migos, was shot and killed in Houston, TMZ reports\r",{"entities":[[58,63,"ORG"],[69,73,"ACT"],[78,84,"ACT"],[88,95,"GPE"],[97,100,"ORG"],[101,108,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: San Francisco DA announces attempted murder charge for alleged Paul Pelosi attacker\r",{"entities":[[11,24,"GPE"],[28,37,"ACT"],[38,47,"ACT"],[66,73,"ACT"],[74,85,"PERSON"]]}],["#BREAKING: Suspect in Paul Pelosi attack in the U .S . illegally .\r",{"entities":[[22,33,"PERSON"],[34,40,"ACT"],[48,54,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING: The Government coordinated the release of media with news outlets, and used their articles to gauge public reaction .\r",{"entities":[[11,25,"ORG"],[26,37,"ACT"],[42,49,"ACT"],[82,86,"ACT"],[105,110,"ACT"]]}],["#BREAKING: The Ontario Science table now predicts a massive Covid wave during cold and flu season where people may experience flu-like symptoms and recommends repeating everything that 's failed over the last 3 years .\r",{"entities":[[11,30,"ORG"],[41,49,"ACT"],[115,125,"ACT"],[148,158,"ACT"],[159,168,"ACT"],[188,194,"ACT"],[200,216,"DATE"]]}],["#BREAKING: The number of injured has risen to over 100 in the Itaewon stampede in #Seoul, according to South Korean security authorities . READ MORE : #SouthKorea\r",{"entities":[[37,42,"ACT"],[62,69,"FAC"],[83,88,"GPE"],[103,136,"ORG"],[139,143,"ACT"],[152,162,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING: Tropical Storm #Lisa forms in the west-central Caribbean . Lisa is forecast to brush by Jamaica &amp; The Cayman Islands over the next couple of days before striking the Yucatan at hurricane intensity later this week . #TropicalUpdate\r",{"entities":[[32,37,"ACT"],[58,67,"GPE"],[70,74,"PERSON"],[90,95,"ACT"],[99,106,"GPE"],[137,160,"DATE"],[168,176,"ACT"],[181,188,"GPE"],[212,227,"DATE"]]}],["#BREAKING: Tropical Storm Lisa has formed in the Caribbean . kiyanalewiswx has the latest on the 12th named storm of the 2022 Atlantic hurricane season .\r",{"entities":[[11,30,"EVENT"],[35,41,"ACT"],[49,58,"GPE"],[61,74,"ORG"],[75,78,"ACT"],[102,107,"ACT"],[121,125,"DATE"],[126,151,"EVENT"]]}],["#BREAKING: Up to 20 people killed, more than 100 others missing following collapse of cable bridge in western India 's Gujarat - Kalinga TV\r",{"entities":[[27,33,"ACT"],[56,63,"ACT"],[64,73,"ACT"],[110,115,"GPE"],[119,126,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING: We now have Tropical Storm #Lisa . Lisa now has a defined circulation to be considered a tropical storm by both recon &amp; visible satellite . In the short term, those in #Jamaica &amp; #CaymanIslands should watch out for potential gusty winds &amp; rainfall . #tropicswx\r",{"entities":[[18,22,"ACT"],[46,50,"PERSON"],[55,58,"ACT"],[61,68,"ACT"],[87,97,"ACT"],[184,191,"GPE"],[220,225,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING_NEWS At least 60 dead, many injured in Gujarat bridge collapse #Gujarat\r",{"entities":[[38,45,"ACT"],[49,63,"FAC"],[64,72,"ACT"],[74,81,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING_NEWS Gujarat Hospital 's Overnight Clean-Up For PM 's Visit after Bridge Tragedy #MorbiBridge\r",{"entities":[[64,69,"ACT"],[76,82,"GPE"]]}],["#BREAKING_NEWS knew “attacker” and events prior were #consensual and sources say involved “favors &amp; money” #underweargate As the stoy unfolds, it appears #PaulPelosi was attacked by his #gay Were Paul Pelosi and his attacker BOTH in their underwear? BOTH holding hammers? And the attacker didn’t strike until AFTER police were on the scene? As a movie-maker, I gotta say this script must be rejected . Nothing about the public account so far makes any sense .\r",{"entities":[[15,19,"ACT"],[77,80,"ACT"],[81,89,"ACT"],[138,145,"ACT"],[150,157,"ACT"],[159,169,"PERSON"],[174,182,"ACT"],[200,215,"PERSON"],[259,266,"ACT"],[300,306,"ACT"],[371,374,"ACT"],[395,403,"ACT"],[446,451,"ACT"]]}],["#Breaking Gujarat Morbi Bridge Collapse w hundreds trapped over Machchhu river suspension span who needed rescue . at least 40 confirmed dead (India ) #Breaking: गुजरात के मोरबी में केबल पुल टूटा, करीब 400 लोग नदी में गिरे, कई के डूबने की आशंका #Gujarat अत्यन्त दुःखद, ईश्वर सबकी रक्षा करें #GujaratModel\r",{"entities":[[10,30,"FAC"],[31,39,"ACT"],[51,58,"ACT"],[64,78,"FAC"],[99,105,"ACT"],[127,136,"ACT"],[143,148,"GPE"],[246,253,"GPE"]]}],["#Breaking of Veer Mandhata Koli Samaj Sangathans in Bhavnagar Gujarat to Join #AAP tomorrow .\r",{"entities":[[52,69,"GPE"],[73,77,"ACT"],[79,82,"ORG"],[83,91,"DATE"]]}],["#Breaking 10 sitting Councillors of Gariadhar Municipality in Gujarat join AAP today in presence of ArvindKejriwal and BhagwantMann Congress Senior Leaders and Many Social Activists also joined AAP Ek Moko Kejriwal Ne!!\r",{"entities":[[13,20,"ACT"],[36,58,"ORG"],[62,69,"ORG"],[70,74,"ACT"],[79,84,"DATE"],[100,114,"PERSON"],[119,131,"PERSON"],[132,140,"ORG"],[187,193,"ACT"]]}],["#Breaking International Atomic Energy Agency (IAEA) experts BEGIN inspection of Ukrainian nuclear facilities following Russian warnings Ukraine is preparing \"DIRTY BOMB\"with IAEA Director Grossi stating 2 facilities are being examinedto detect any possible UNDECLAREDnukes\r",{"entities":[[10,44,"ORG"],[46,50,"ORG"],[60,65,"ACT"],[80,89,"NORP"],[109,118,"ACT"],[119,126,"NORP"],[136,143,"GPE_WHO"],[147,156,"ACT"],[188,194,"PERSON"],[195,202,"ACT"],[237,243,"ACT"]]}],["#Breaking :— Congress president kharge Ji will visit Gujarat on 29th October . With his visit , Gujarat congress is going to gear up its preparation for assembly election .\r",{"entities":[[13,21,"ORG"],[32,38,"PERSON"],[47,52,"ACT"],[53,60,"GPE"],[64,76,"DATE"],[88,93,"ACT"],[96,103,"GPE"],[116,121,"ACT"],[125,129,"ACT"]]}],["#Breaking Alert Flash floods and landslides set off by torrential rains swamped a southern Philippine province, killing at least 31 people, leaving nine others missing and trapping some residents on their roofs, officials said Friday . #Philippine\r",{"entities":[[44,47,"ACT"],[72,79,"ACT"],[91,101,"NORP"],[112,119,"ACT"],[140,147,"ACT"],[160,167,"ACT"],[172,180,"ACT"],[222,226,"ACT"],[227,233,"DATE"]]}],["#Breaking news out of Houston 1 killed, 2 injured in surgery at hospital after a shooting in downtown Houston . There’s a lot of online speculation on victim, police won’t say who the vics are but said, members of Migos were in attendance, specifically Quavo and TakeOff KPRC2\r",{"entities":[[22,29,"GPE"],[32,38,"ACT"],[42,49,"ACT"],[102,109,"GPE"],[172,175,"ACT"],[197,201,"ACT"],[214,219,"ORG"],[253,258,"ORG"]]}],["#Breaking | Centre Grants Power To Two Gujarat District Collectors To Give Citizenship To Afghanistan, Pakistan, Bangladesh Minorities anjalipandey06\r",{"entities":[[39,46,"GPE"],[70,74,"ACT"],[90,101,"GPE"],[103,111,"GPE"],[113,123,"GPE"]]}],["#Breaking: A cable bridge in Morbi, Gujarat collapsed . About 400+ people are reported to have fallen into the river . Several of them are said to have drowned . #Gujarat\r",{"entities":[[29,34,"GPE"],[36,43,"GPE"],[44,53,"ACT"],[78,86,"ACT"],[95,101,"ACT"],[139,143,"ACT"],[152,159,"ACT"],[163,170,"GPE"]]}],["#BreakingNews Update - South Korea cancels concerts, government briefings after Itaewon stampede\r",{"entities":[[23,34,"GPE"],[35,42,"ACT"],[64,73,"ACT"],[80,87,"GPE"]]}],["#BreakingNews: There were 500 people on the bridge in Morbi, Gujarat and so far 60 people have died and 80 injured people have been rescued due to the bridge falling in the water . #BREAKING\r",{"entities":[[21,25,"ACT"],[54,59,"GPE"],[61,68,"GPE"],[95,99,"ACT"],[107,114,"ACT"],[132,139,"ACT"],[158,165,"ACT"]]}],["#Breaking_News: Several cargo ships, loaded with #grain left #Ukraine ports on Tuesday . A senior Ukraine official said one of the vessels is carrying 40,000 tons of grain destined for #Ethiopia .\r",{"entities":[[37,43,"ACT"],[56,60,"ACT"],[62,69,"GPE"],[79,86,"DATE"],[98,105,"GPE"],[115,119,"ACT"],[142,150,"ACT"],[172,180,"ACT"],[186,194,"GPE"]]}],["#COVID19 MT ‘Breaking news JUST IN Tokyo - 6,520 new cases, 10 consecutive days higher than the previous week .’ #nhk_news JUST IN 56520 10 #nhk_news\r",{"entities":[[35,40,"GPE"],[60,79,"DATE"],[92,109,"DATE"]]}],["#Gujarat Suspension Bridge that collapsed due to overloading . Suspension Bridge in BJP’s Gujarat collapsed . More than 400 people fell into water and got injured! To be noted that, this bridge was renovated &amp; opened just 5 days ago . This is Gujarat’s development\r",{"entities":[[1,8,"GPE"],[32,41,"ACT"],[84,89,"ORG"],[90,97,"GPE"],[98,107,"ACT"],[131,135,"ACT"],[155,162,"ACT"],[170,175,"ACT"],[198,207,"ACT"],[214,220,"ACT"],[221,236,"DATE"],[247,256,"GPE"]]}],["#Gujarat: The death toll in the Morbi suspension bridge collapse rose to 134, a senior Gujarat police official said, adding that the rescue operation was still underway . #GujaratPolice\r",{"entities":[[1,8,"GPE"],[32,37,"PERSON"],[65,69,"ACT"],[87,94,"GPE"],[111,115,"ACT"],[117,123,"ACT"]]}],["#GujaratBridgeCollapse | Prime Minister Narendra Modi to visit Morbi, Gujarat tomorrow (November 1) -via ANI\r",{"entities":[[40,53,"PERSON"],[57,62,"ACT"],[63,68,"GPE"],[70,77,"GPE"],[78,86,"DATE"],[88,98,"DATE"]]}],["#GujratCableBridge Very unfortunate! Almost 400 people fell into the river . This is symbolic of the ensuing days BJP4India in its #Hindutvalab and elsewhere in India Gujarat Cable Bridge Collapses: Rescue Operations On | Breaking News | N ... via YouTube\r",{"entities":[[55,59,"ACT"],[97,113,"DATE"],[132,143,"ORG"],[161,166,"GPE"],[167,187,"FAC"],[188,197,"ACT"],[199,205,"ACT"],[248,255,"ORG"]]}],["#JusticeForNoahDonohoe Twitter Storm today, and every Sunday, at 6:11pm \"If you can whistle, ride a bike and blow a bubble, you can do anything .\" RIP Noah Donohoe, Passed on, June 2020, aged 14years\r",{"entities":[[37,42,"DATE"],[48,60,"DATE"],[65,71,"TIME"],[84,91,"ACT"],[93,97,"ACT"],[109,113,"ACT"],[132,134,"ACT"],[151,163,"PERSON"],[165,171,"ACT"],[176,185,"DATE"],[192,199,"DATE"]]}],["#LIVE | Republic 's crew physically targeted after questioning Chief Minister of Gujarat over the Morbi Bridge Collapse; Tune in for #BREAKING updates here -\r",{"entities":[[36,44,"ACT"],[51,62,"ACT"],[81,88,"GPE"],[94,110,"FAC"],[111,119,"ACT"],[121,125,"ACT"]]}],["#MarineCorps F-35 Lightning II aircraft from Marine Fighter Attack Squadron 242 land at Kunsan Air Base, Republic of Korea, for Exercise Vigilant Storm 23, Oct . 31 #VigilantStorm enhances combat readiness and strengthens the ROK-U .S . Alliance . #CombinedForce\r",{"entities":[[80,84,"ACT"],[88,103,"FAC"],[117,122,"GPE"],[156,164,"DATE"],[180,188,"ACT"],[210,221,"ACT"]]}],["#NowPlaying God 's Property &amp; Kirk Franklin - The Storm Is Over Now CLICK WEBSITE TO LISTEN #NP adamology1 #Adamology\r",{"entities":[[34,47,"PERSON"],[72,77,"ACT"],[89,95,"ACT"]]}],["#OTD is the anniversary of the powerful 1755 earthquake that hit the Iberian Peninsula . Widespread environmental effects allowed to assign ESI intensity of XI\r",{"entities":[[61,64,"ACT"],[65,86,"LOC"],[122,129,"ACT"],[133,139,"ACT"],[140,143,"ORG"]]}],["#OnThisDay 1st Nov, an earthquake struck Lisbon in 1755. Read a first hand account of the tragedy here:\r",{"entities":[[11,18,"DATE"],[34,40,"ACT"],[41,47,"GPE"],[51,56,"DATE"],[57,61,"ACT"]]}],["#PaengPH | PROJECT LUSOB The City of Tuguegarao is in devastating floods once again caused by the heavy rains last night and constant release of water from the Magat dam due to the tropical storm #PaengPH .\r",{"entities":[[25,47,"GPE"],[84,90,"ACT"],[110,120,"TIME"],[134,141,"ACT"],[160,169,"FAC"]]}],["#TyphoonPaengPH 4th in a row to hit the Philippines in 2022 not to mention the recent earthquake! Please think of, pray for and help the poorest communities that will bear the brunt of Paeng . Every damn year! Big sigh .. WATCH: Real-time Himawari satellite images of Tropical Storm #PaengPH as it moves closer towards Northern Samar, Sorsogon, and Albay areas . | : JMA-Himawari via johnsamuelyap\r",{"entities":[[32,35,"ACT"],[40,51,"GPE"],[55,59,"DATE"],[67,74,"ACT"],[105,110,"ACT"],[115,119,"ACT"],[128,132,"ACT"],[167,171,"ACT"],[193,208,"DATE"],[222,227,"ACT"],[239,257,"FAC"],[298,303,"ACT"],[319,333,"GPE"],[335,343,"GPE"],[349,360,"GPE"]]}],["#UPDATE Dozens of people suffered from cardiac arrest in the South Korean capital Seoul on Saturday, after thousands crowded into narrow streets in the city 's Itaewon neighbourhood to celebrate Halloween, local officials said AFP story here:",{"entities":[[25,33,"ACT"],[61,73,"NORP"],[82,87,"GPE"],[91,99,"DATE"],[117,124,"ACT"],[160,167,"GPE"],[185,194,"ACT"],[195,204,"DATE"],[222,226,"ACT"]]}],["#Update: Crush in Korea 's Itaewon claims 151 lives, 19 foreign deaths reported #ItaewonStampede\r",{"entities":[[18,23,"GPE"],[27,34,"GPE"],[35,41,"ACT"],[71,79,"ACT"]]}],["#WalangPasok: Classes for Wednesday, November 2, 2022, have been canceled in some areas still reeling from the onslaught of Severe Tropical Storm Paeng . Refresh this page for updates .\r",{"entities":[[26,53,"DATE"],[65,73,"ACT"],[94,101,"ACT"],[124,151,"EVENT"],[154,161,"ACT"]]}],["#XiaoZhan His silent deeds break borders and change lives . Wholeheartedly influence his fans to do charity nationwide . COvid, nursing homes, hospitals, earthquake victims, local workers . HE SPREADS LOVE TO EVERYONE HE TOUCHED WITH HIS LIGHT #NETIZENSREPORT\r",{"entities":[[27,32,"ACT"],[45,51,"ACT"],[75,84,"ACT"],[97,99,"ACT"],[193,200,"ACT"],[201,205,"ACT"],[221,228,"ACT"]]}],["'Create hazard maps' for disaster planning Prof . Mahar Lagmay of the UP Resilience Institute has this suggestion to the government following the onslaught of Severe Tropical Storm #PaengPH which triggered flash floods and landslides in parts of the country .\r",{"entities":[[50,62,"PERSON"],[66,93,"ORG"],[94,97,"ACT"],[132,141,"ACT"],[196,205,"ACT"]]}],["'Disturbing' conspiracy theory takes root following Pelosi attack #Biden\r",{"entities":[[31,36,"ACT"],[42,51,"ACT"],[52,58,"PERSON"],[59,65,"ACT"]]}],["'Ghalat Ladki' is a very derogatory &amp; unacceptable word for any girl . Sad Priyanka is using this word for herself, God Bless Her If #Shalin ud have used this for her, then there ud be an earthquake in the house n on WKV . #ShalinBhanot EndemolShineIND #BiggBoss16 Shalin aur Priyanka ke beech badha gussa, kya iss fight se badal jaayega ghar ka vatavaran? Dekhiye #BiggBoss16 Mon-Fri raat 10 baje aur Sat-Sun raat 9.30 baje, sirf #Colors par . Anytime on justvoot #BB16 beingsalmankhan\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[79,87,"PERSON"],[91,96,"ACT"],[124,129,"ACT"],[153,157,"ACT"],[221,224,"GPE"],[319,324,"ACT"],[381,388,"DATE"],[430,434,"PERSON"]]}],["'Words fail': Tapper breaks down conspiracy theories about Paul Pelosi attack #Biden\r",{"entities":[[7,11,"ACT"],[14,20,"PERSON"],[21,27,"ACT"],[59,70,"PERSON"],[71,77,"ACT"],[79,84,"PERSON"]]}],["(Breaking Down The Digital Footprint Of Paul Pelosi Attack Suspect) has been published on News Lookout - #newslookout\r",{"entities":[[1,9,"ACT"],[40,51,"PERSON"],[77,86,"ACT"]]}],["*BREAKING: New Tropical Storm Lisa seen likely to reach hurricane status before making landfall on Honduras coast later this week &amp; dumping HEAVY rains across most of CentAm &amp; southern Mexico, very dangerous for people &amp; #coffee with lands saturated and vulnerable to landslides!!\r",{"entities":[[11,34,"EVENT"],[50,55,"ACT"],[80,86,"ACT"],[99,107,"GPE"],[114,129,"DATE"],[136,143,"ACT"],[193,199,"GPE"]]}],["*Breaking news* Our commodities’ trading business is expanding . We have acquired Cotton Distributors Inc . (CDI). CDI has a successful track record of opening new outlets for cotton and has been trading in cotton for over 20 years .\r",{"entities":[[53,62,"ACT"],[73,81,"ACT"],[82,105,"ORG"],[109,112,"ORG"],[115,118,"ORG"],[119,122,"ACT"],[152,159,"ACT"],[196,203,"ACT"],[223,231,"DATE"]]}],["+ military dictatorship in Myanmar since 2021 Feb but no one wants to help us enthusiastically . The UN is just worried about us :)) They don't do anything except that while people in my country including children are dying . Rip, victims in Itaewon . floods in pakistan and brazil, typhoons in philippines, earthquakes in china and afghanistan and most recently a bridge collapsing in india all in 2022 alone .. but you only make this tweet about itaewon because korea = kpopland, right??\r",{"entities":[[27,34,"GPE"],[41,45,"DATE"],[46,49,"DATE"],[61,66,"ACT"],[70,74,"ACT"],[101,103,"ORG"],[144,146,"ACT"],[195,204,"ACT"],[218,223,"ACT"],[242,249,"GPE"],[262,270,"GPE"],[275,281,"GPE"],[295,306,"GPE"],[323,328,"GPE"],[333,344,"GPE"],[372,382,"ACT"],[386,391,"GPE"],[399,403,"DATE"],[426,430,"ACT"],[448,455,"GPE"],[464,469,"GPE"]]}],["- BREAKING: Iran will sign $40 billion dollar deal with Russian energy giant Gazprom to develop oil and gas fields in the Islamic Republic Iran 's Oil Minister has also stated that talks are underway to establish a joint \"Economic Free Zone\" between Russia and Iran .\r",{"entities":[[12,16,"GPE_WHO"],[22,26,"ACT"],[56,63,"NORP"],[77,84,"ORG"],[88,95,"ACT"],[139,143,"GPE"],[169,175,"ACT"],[203,212,"ACT"],[222,240,"WORK_OF_ART"],[250,256,"GPE"],[261,265,"GPE"]]}],[".ChloeBailey was named on this year’s Most Impressive Celebrity Costumes list by TIME for her X-Men Storm cosplay\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[17,22,"ACT"],[94,99,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}],["0.78 magnitude earthquake occurred at San Diego, CA, United States on 2022-11-01 10:01:27 UTC Map: #earthb0t\r",{"entities":[[26,34,"ACT"],[38,47,"GPE"],[49,51,"GPE"],[53,66,"GPE"],[70,80,"DATE"],[81,89,"TIME"]]}],["0.94 magnitude earthquake occurred at Trona Rd, Trona, CA 93562, United States on 2022-11-01 09:33:59 UTC Map: #earthb0t\r",{"entities":[[26,34,"ACT"],[48,53,"GPE"],[55,57,"GPE"],[65,78,"GPE"],[82,92,"DATE"],[93,101,"TIME"]]}],["0.97 magnitude earthquake occurred at Eagle Rock Rd, Cloverdale, CA 95425, United States on 2022-11-01 12:00:42 UTC Map: #earthb0t\r",{"entities":[[26,34,"ACT"],[38,51,"GPE"],[53,63,"GPE"],[65,67,"GPE"],[75,88,"GPE"],[92,102,"DATE"],[103,111,"TIME"]]}],["1.15 magnitude earthquake occurred at 886 Shevlin Dr, El Cerrito, CA 94530-3051, United States on 2022-11-01 12:18:58 UTC Map: #earthb0t\r",{"entities":[[26,34,"ACT"],[38,52,"FAC"],[54,64,"GPE"],[66,68,"GPE"],[81,94,"GPE"],[98,108,"DATE"],[109,117,"TIME"]]}],["10/10 “A skateboarder nosily pushing ...crafting concrete transitions in a derelict parking lot, or kickflipping on roads mangled by an earthquake are all moments of challenge to the almost invisible elegance of the way capitalism suffocates our creativity and steals our labour .”\r",{"entities":[[29,36,"ACT"],[40,48,"ACT"],[100,112,"ACT"],[122,129,"ACT"],[231,241,"ACT"],[261,267,"ACT"]]}],["16 Oct Vietnam – Thousands Displaced by Floods After Storm Sonca Dumps 500mm of Rain 16 Oct Deadly flash flooding batters Greek island of Crete 14 Oct Severe flash floods hit Sicily, Italy 12/\r",{"entities":[[0,6,"DATE"],[7,14,"GPE"],[27,36,"ACT"],[80,91,"EVENT"],[105,113,"ACT"],[122,127,"NORP"],[144,150,"DATE"],[171,174,"ACT"],[175,181,"GPE"],[183,188,"GPE"]]}],["2.21 magnitude earthquake occurred at Hawaii, HI, United States on 2022-11-01 11:10:43 UTC Map: #earthb0t\r",{"entities":[[26,34,"ACT"],[38,44,"GPE"],[46,48,"GPE"],[50,63,"GPE"],[67,77,"DATE"],[78,86,"TIME"]]}],["2/10 Skateboarders seem like opportunists: taking advantage of empty pools, riding spaces built for commerce like stairs, handrails, curbs . Even, as hollythorpe_nz discovered, earthquake “destroyed” freeways . But, skaters are more like disaster artists!\r",{"entities":[[19,23,"ACT"],[43,49,"ACT"],[76,82,"ACT"],[90,95,"ACT"],[165,175,"ACT"],[188,199,"ACT"]]}],["2021 and 2022 comparison in AGS Colony, Velachery after Storm Water Drain Construction Remarkable work by DMK Government Credits - GeethaGKarthik 1/2 mkstalin #chennairains\r",{"entities":[[0,4,"DATE"],[9,13,"DATE"],[28,38,"GPE"],[40,49,"GPE"],[106,109,"ORG"]]}],["25mm Warhammer 40K DPS painted Space Marines Storm Speeder Thunderstrike TP7140 eBay\r",{"entities":[[23,30,"ACT"]]}],["3.91 magnitude earthquake occurred at Fire Road 14, Kamuela, HI 96743, United States on 2022-11-01 11:17:27 UTC Map: #earthb0t\r",{"entities":[[26,34,"ACT"],[38,50,"FAC"],[52,59,"GPE"],[61,63,"GPE"],[71,84,"GPE"],[88,98,"DATE"],[99,107,"TIME"]]}],["31 Oct Cameroon – Floods Destroy Almost 20,000 Homes in Far North 29 Oct Storm Nalgae: floods and landslides in Philippines kill at least 72 3/\r",{"entities":[[0,15,"DATE"],[25,32,"ACT"],[56,65,"LOC"],[66,72,"DATE"],[112,123,"GPE"],[124,128,"ACT"]]}],["4.1-magnitude earthquake jolts northern Chinese city of Tangshan . (Apr . 9, 2010)\r",{"entities":[[25,30,"ACT"],[40,47,"GPE"],[56,64,"GPE"],[68,81,"DATE"]]}],["4.3-magnitude earthquake strikes #Goesan in central #SouthKorea I did not expect to hear the high pitched earthquake alarm in South Korea but here we are . Yonhap reports 4.3 magnitude in Goesan, the centre of the country\r",{"entities":[[25,32,"ACT"],[34,40,"GPE"],[53,63,"GPE"],[74,80,"ACT"],[84,88,"ACT"],[98,105,"ACT"],[126,137,"GPE"],[156,162,"ORG"],[163,170,"ACT"],[188,194,"GPE"]]}],["4.54 earthquake close to New Zealand at 11:58 UTC! #earthquake\r",{"entities":[[25,36,"GPE"],[40,49,"TIME"]]}],["45 dead as Tropical Storm Nalgae hits Philippines – CNN\r",{"entities":[[33,37,"ACT"],[38,49,"GPE"],[50,55,"ORG"]]}],["5.57 pm Breaking (by Hankyoreh): Yongsan-gu Police requested that subway pass without stopping at Itaewon Station only an hour after stampede in alley near Hamilton . 159 were dead, still counting . Proof very chaotic in station (photos) Live Update:\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"TIME"],[21,30,"PERSON"],[33,43,"GPE"],[51,60,"ACT"],[86,94,"ACT"],[98,105,"GPE"],[114,126,"TIME"],[156,164,"GPE"],[188,196,"ACT"]]}],["5.7-magnitude earthquake strikes northeastern Taiwan Taiwan news\r",{"entities":[[25,32,"ACT"],[46,52,"GPE"],[53,64,"ORG"]]}],["5:20am Tuesday, November 01, 2022: Tuesday morning 's satellite images show Tropical Storm Lisa southwest of Jamaica, but left over moisture from her previous broad area of low pressure can be seen south of Hispaniola that will bring rain to parts Jamaica today into tomorrow .\r",{"entities":[[0,6,"TIME"],[7,33,"DATE"],[35,42,"DATE"],[43,50,"DATE"],[71,75,"ACT"],[76,95,"EVENT"],[109,116,"GPE"],[122,126,"ACT"],[193,197,"ACT"],[207,217,"GPE"],[228,233,"ACT"],[248,255,"GPE"],[256,261,"DATE"],[267,275,"DATE"]]}],["72 dead as Tropical Storm Nalgae hits Philippines #Biden\r",{"entities":[[33,37,"ACT"],[38,49,"GPE"],[51,56,"PERSON"]]}],["1857_Viplav Even Hafiz Said was very active when earthquake hit Pakistan . What’s your point?\r",{"entities":[[60,63,"ACT"],[64,72,"GPE"]]}],["7AFL Breaking news: Jack Ginnivan dresses up as a scary character on Halloween .\r",{"entities":[[20,33,"PERSON"],[34,41,"ACT"],[69,78,"DATE"]]}],["ABC71766771 1. He didn't . The attacker called himself a friend 2. The glass was broken with a small instrument: a hammer . Breaking glass with that vs . a large heavy object with momentum will cause the glass to shatter everywhere, not exclusively toward the inside 3. Pelosi ran to open the\r",{"entities":[[18,21,"ACT"],[40,46,"ACT"],[81,87,"ACT"],[124,132,"ACT"],[194,199,"ACT"],[213,220,"ACT"],[270,276,"PERSON"],[277,280,"ACT"],[284,288,"ACT"]]}],["ANI BIG BREAKING NEWS : PM &amp; his photographers are going visit Morbi, Gujarat tomorrow #Morbi\r",{"entities":[[0,3,"ORG"],[55,60,"ACT"],[67,72,"GPE"],[74,81,"GPE"],[82,90,"DATE"]]}],["AdyBee9 Disaster Capitalism - some Corporations and Governments have been doing very nicely out of \"helping\" countries get back on their feet after a disaster . They got bored waiting for the next tsunami, famine, earthquake or war - and started initiating events .\r",{"entities":[[74,79,"ACT"],[100,107,"ACT"],[119,122,"ACT"],[166,169,"ACT"],[170,175,"ACT"],[176,183,"ACT"],[238,245,"ACT"],[246,256,"ACT"]]}],["AlpuertoMary Breaking news! Congratz Mary!\r",{"entities":[[37,41,"PERSON"]]}],["Ayrtanium He 's gonna cause a fuckin earthquake that 's what",{"entities":[[22,27,"ACT"]]}],["BBCBreaking Breaking news! Talentless little skid mark takes part in one of the worst shows on TV .\r",{"entities":[[55,60,"ACT"]]}],["BTS_JIN_SJ BREAKING Over 100 people experience cardiac arrest after crowd surge in Itaewon where thousands gathered for Halloween\r",{"entities":[[47,54,"ACT"],[83,90,"GPE"],[107,115,"ACT"],[120,129,"DATE"]]}],["BeatTheCult \"Ethics are great but ethics are a secondary or tertiary move for Christians . The first move is to witness to an earthquake - the resurrection of Jesus Christ . Ethics will follow from that down the pike but what matters first is the resurrection of Jesus .\"\r",{"entities":[[78,88,"NORP"],[159,171,"PERSON"],[186,192,"ACT"],[226,233,"ACT"],[263,268,"PERSON"]]}],["Capt_Navy I know I’m supposed to adore him, but dropped after “Clear and Present Danger .” I fucking loved “Red Storm Rising,” though . Loved . It .\r",{"entities":[[12,16,"ACT"],[21,29,"ACT"],[33,38,"ACT"],[48,55,"ACT"],[63,87,"WORK_OF_ART"],[101,106,"ACT"],[108,124,"WORK_OF_ART"]]}],["CarolineLucas Breaking news, he has lost the whip for appearing in the program\r",{"entities":[[36,40,"ACT"],[54,63,"ACT"]]}],["Catholic4Choice BREAKING: Paul Pelosi Attacker is an ILLEGAL IMMIGRANT Residing in America ILLEGALLY due to BROKEN JOE BIDEN IMMIGRATION LAWS, OVERSTAYED VISA, ZERO IMMIGRATION ENFORCEMENT and Criminal DHS Negligence .\r",{"entities":[[0,15,"ORG"],[26,37,"PERSON"],[71,79,"ACT"],[83,90,"GPE"],[108,114,"ACT"],[115,124,"PERSON"],[143,153,"ACT"],[154,158,"ORG"],[202,205,"ORG"]]}],["CrazyNomura The Lightning Storm from the Crystals Breaking fighting the Child Chaos gathered as the World\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[12,31,"WORK_OF_ART"],[59,67,"ACT"],[84,92,"ACT"]]}],["DailyPostNGR May earthquake swallow you and your government, Amen .\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[28,35,"ACT"]]}],["DavidCornDC When republicans try to act like there had never been riots n looting when that 's always happen in America for whatever reason during hurricane floods earthquake blockouts marches sports championship wins n losses\r",{"entities":[[17,28,"NORP"],[29,32,"ACT"],[36,39,"ACT"],[66,71,"ACT"],[102,108,"ACT"],[112,119,"GPE"],[185,192,"ACT"],[213,217,"ACT"]]}],["Dexerto Breaking news WE DONT CARE\r",{"entities":[[30,34,"ACT"]]}],["DineshDSouza BREAKING NEWS!!! Leaked footage on how Paul Pelosi was injured .\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[30,36,"ACT"],[52,63,"PERSON"],[68,75,"ACT"]]}],["DougJBalloon Breaking news: Musk to buy hammer manufacturer .\r",{"entities":[[28,32,"PERSON"],[36,39,"ACT"]]}],["FoxNews Breaking news! Pelosi has proof that her ingrown toenail was caused by Trump!\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"],[23,29,"PERSON"],[30,33,"ACT"],[69,75,"ACT"],[79,84,"PERSON"]]}],["FoxNews Breaking news!! Nancy Pelosi is positioning herself to be the President of the USA! Think about it . Joe resigns (for one of the many good reasons) Kamala declines and Nancy kindly allows Kamala to continue to be VP . IT COULD HAPPEN SOON\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"],[24,36,"PERSON"],[40,51,"ACT"],[87,90,"GPE"],[92,97,"ACT"],[109,112,"PERSON"],[113,120,"ACT"],[156,162,"PERSON"],[163,171,"ACT"],[176,181,"PERSON"],[189,195,"ACT"],[196,202,"PERSON"],[206,214,"ACT"],[235,241,"ACT"]]}],["Funwithflares Breaking news . Man goes out with his mates after work and has fun .\r",{"entities":[[34,38,"ACT"],[73,76,"ACT"]]}],["GeologyPage And it 's been a long time since it has shifted . My question is when the next major earthquake happens will democrats blame it on climate change?\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[52,59,"ACT"],[108,115,"ACT"],[121,130,"NORP"],[131,136,"ACT"]]}],["J0E007 Breaking news #Elon fuks all twitter employees Has new #tesla love drug YOU WAKE UP FUCKED\r",{"entities":[[54,57,"ACT"],[63,68,"ORG"],[69,73,"ACT"],[83,87,"ACT"],[91,97,"ACT"]]}],["JaviciaLeslie I'd be down if Marvel gets You to be Storm in the MCU!\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[29,35,"ORG"],[36,40,"ACT"],[64,67,"ORG"]]}],["JayJurden Storm was an Avenger for all of, what, a week? Two missions before AvX?\r",{"entities":[[49,56,"DATE"],[77,80,"ORG"]]}],["Josh_oknefski I’m in Houston right now, so floods and hurricanes . I was in SoCal previously - fires and the 1994 earthquake . I also lived in NE Ohio near where the 1985 Newton Falls F5 hit .\r",{"entities":[[0,13,"PERSON"],[21,28,"GPE"],[76,81,"GPE"],[109,113,"DATE"],[134,139,"ACT"],[143,150,"GPE"],[166,170,"DATE"]]}],["KasulisK People have become numb to tragedy . By next week we will have moved on from Itaewon and on to the next big thing! I mean who even remembers the destruction caused by hurricane Ian in Florida and calamities of all the floods around the world this year?\r",{"entities":[[21,27,"ACT"],[36,43,"ACT"],[49,58,"DATE"],[72,77,"ACT"],[86,93,"GPE"],[126,130,"ACT"],[140,149,"ACT"],[166,172,"ACT"],[193,200,"GPE"],[251,260,"DATE"]]}],["Katekathryn1 Now how does it concern you till you call it bad news did it cause earthquake to your village\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[29,36,"ACT"],[50,54,"ACT"],[74,79,"ACT"]]}],["KiranaYonome Breaking news . This just in . Local cat girl breaks the internet by sneezing into her camera . The internet is said to be still recovering from this incident . Thankfully, no netizens were hurt in the wake of this catastrophe . Next is Bob Miller with the weather . Back to you Bob .\r",{"entities":[[59,65,"ACT"],[82,90,"ACT"],[125,129,"ACT"],[142,152,"ACT"],[203,207,"ACT"],[250,260,"PERSON"],[292,295,"PERSON"]]}],["KyivIndependent BREAKING Russia will send up to 500,000 tons of its own grain to the poorest countries, particularly in Africa, free of charge in the next 4 months .\r",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[25,31,"GPE_WHO"],[37,41,"ACT"],[120,126,"LOC"],[146,163,"DATE"]]}],["LegionHoops Breaking news: Primo signs 5 year contract with the Cleveland Browns .\r",{"entities":[[27,32,"PERSON"],[33,38,"ACT"],[39,45,"DATE"],[60,80,"ORG"]]}],["Liz_Wheeler BREAKING: Paul Pelosi attacker is a Black-hating, Trans-Hating, Jew-Hating, Democrat-Hating Right-wing kook\r",{"entities":[[22,33,"PERSON"]]}],["Mahesh10816 Where No earthquake may occur Pray to Gods .\r",{"entities":[[21,31,"ACT"],[42,46,"ACT"]]}],["MaraLiasson October 18, 2018 Nancy Pelosi: Voters will have to deal w“collateral damage” if Democrats craft economic policies in the years ahead .\" ABC Dec 18 2019 BREAKING: House Speaker Nancy Pelosi remarks ..\"Any collateral damage to the nation just too bad--we don't care\".\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[12,28,"DATE"],[29,41,"PERSON"],[55,59,"ACT"],[92,101,"NORP"],[129,138,"DATE"],[148,151,"ORG"],[152,163,"DATE"],[188,200,"PERSON"],[271,276,"ACT"]]}],["MattWalshBlog BREAKING NEWS!!! Leaked footage on how Paul Pelosi was injured .\r",{"entities":[[31,37,"ACT"],[53,64,"PERSON"],[69,76,"ACT"]]}],["Michell33650674 Just an earthquake (and it is really only just one worthy) and tornadoes/storms to worry about . ;-)",{"entities":[[99,104,"ACT"]]}],["MonsterPanPan I like to think of him as my earthquake detector droid .\r",{"entities":[[16,20,"ACT"],[24,29,"ACT"]]}],["Morning_Joe   news - Jason Bourne gets through secret service detail while only wearing underwear and carrying a hammer . -if you believe that well .... good luck , misinformation or willful sheep are useless\r",{"entities":[[21,33,"PERSON"],[34,38,"ACT"],[80,87,"ACT"],[102,110,"ACT"],[130,137,"ACT"]]}],["NBCNews   news tiny Tim leaves twitter\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ORG"],[20,23,"PERSON"],[24,30,"ACT"]]}],["PMOIndia Are you PM of Gujarat alone ? Wbt the farmers in Maharashtra that have been pushed to sucide due to floods earlier & amp ; wet drought now ? If you can declare help for these victims within hours then why do the farmers have to beg ? AUThackeray\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"GPE"],[23,30,"GPE"],[39,42,"PERSON"],[58,69,"GPE"],[85,91,"ACT"],[161,168,"ACT"],[192,204,"TIME"],[229,233,"ACT"],[237,240,"ACT"]]}],["PMOIndia Gujarat bridge collapse : At least 32 dead as cable bridge collapses in Gujarat 's Morbi , several feared trapped Download the TOI app now : Panuti\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"],[9,23,"FAC"],[68,77,"ACT"],[81,88,"GPE"],[92,97,"GPE"],[108,114,"ACT"],[123,131,"ACT"],[136,139,"ORG"],[150,156,"PERSON"]]}],["PMOIndia Panuti of man ki baat Gujarat bridge collapse : At least 32 dead as cable bridge collapses in Gujarat 's Morbi , several feared trapped Download the TOI app now :\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"],[31,45,"FAC"],[90,99,"ACT"],[103,110,"GPE"],[114,119,"GPE"],[130,136,"ACT"],[145,153,"ACT"],[158,161,"ORG"]]}],["PMOIndia What a quality of rennovation .... Atma nirbhar hogayi Gujarat bridge collapse : At least 32 dead as cable bridge collapses in Gujarat 's Morbi , several feared trapped Download the TOI app now :\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"ORG"],[44,48,"PERSON"],[64,78,"FAC"],[79,87,"ACT"],[123,132,"ACT"],[136,143,"GPE"],[147,152,"GPE"],[163,169,"ACT"],[178,186,"ACT"],[191,194,"ORG"]]}],["Perpetualmaniac   : ‘ new security video emerges from the Pelosi residence . ’\r",{"entities":[[41,48,"ACT"],[58,64,"PERSON"]]}],["PolticalJunkee Riots n looting happen during hurricane floods earthquake etc marches n sports championship\r",{"entities":[[31,37,"ACT"]]}],["RealEstateMaxi Anything wrong with the land is unfixable + high insurance costs . • High wildfire risk • High flood risk • High hurricane / tornado risk • At foot of prior landslide • High water table • & lt;500 ft from earthquake fault • & lt;500 from fwy • Foundation issues , ground subsidence\r",{"entities":[[270,276,"ACT"]]}],["RealMaxtern   news NeonMan_01 It 's confirm RealMaxtern support Aman\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[19,29,"PERSON"],[36,43,"ACT"],[44,55,"PERSON"],[64,68,"PERSON"]]}],["RevatiSharma15 During the 2013 flash floods in Uttharakhand it was reported that Modi flew a massive jet and rescued a lot of people from Gujarat who were stuck in the mountains . What is preventing him from doing it now ?\r",{"entities":[[26,30,"DATE"],[47,59,"GPE"],[67,75,"ACT"],[81,85,"PERSON"],[86,90,"ACT"],[109,116,"ACT"],[138,145,"GPE"],[155,160,"ACT"],[188,198,"ACT"],[208,213,"ACT"]]}],["SarkySage2 Morning Sage .   news : Brought to you by the # LNP You are not cold It is not raining in Brisbane Gravity is not real Michelle Landry really was bullied # LandryGate McKenzie is smart We will now return you to our regular programming # auspol\r",{"entities":[[35,42,"ACT"],[90,97,"ACT"],[101,109,"GPE"],[130,145,"PERSON"],[157,164,"ACT"],[178,186,"PERSON"],[208,214,"ACT"]]}],["ScotExpress   news . Unionism has done nothing for Scot ’s for over 300 years .\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[34,38,"ACT"],[51,55,"ORG"],[63,77,"DATE"]]}],["ScotNational   news he ’s not a celebrity he ’s a criminal !\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[45,47,"ACT"]]}],["SoWarrior   news - Jason Bourne gets through secret service detail while only wearing underwear and carrying a hammer . -if you believe that well .... good luck\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"ORG"],[19,31,"PERSON"],[32,36,"ACT"],[78,85,"ACT"],[100,108,"ACT"],[128,135,"ACT"]]}],["StormySturgeon More chance of a massive earthquake hitting the border than the SNP getting anywhere other than where they are just now . Nowhere . I predict a year today , nothing changed , no Indy ref 2 , ferries further delayed . Humza still Health minister with thousands dead !\r",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[51,58,"ACT"],[79,82,"ORG"],[83,90,"ACT"],[149,156,"ACT"],[157,163,"DATE"],[164,169,"DATE"],[180,187,"ACT"],[193,197,"ORG"],[222,229,"ACT"],[232,237,"PERSON"]]}],["TBwinningtheWS   news : after being inspired by this guys tweet the XFL has announced they will be relocating 3 teams to match cities named on this list . The new teams will be : Orlando Guardians St . Louis Battlehawks San Antonio Brahmas\r",{"entities":[[36,44,"ACT"],[58,63,"ACT"],[68,71,"ORG"],[76,85,"ACT"],[99,109,"ACT"],[121,126,"ACT"],[134,139,"ACT"],[179,196,"ORG"],[197,219,"ORG"],[220,239,"ORG"]]}],["TahirMughalPml2   news : fitay moun\r",{"entities":[[25,30,"PERSON"]]}],["TahirMughalPml2   news : mariyum nawaz said she will never come back to Pakistan again and no more interested in politics , house wife bnay gi ab sy\r",{"entities":[[39,43,"ACT"],[59,63,"ACT"],[72,80,"GPE"]]}],["TheInsiderPaper How is this   news when I already read it four days ago ?\r",{"entities":[[50,54,"ACT"],[58,71,"DATE"]]}],["ThessusD \"   news : Local store workers HATE this specimen \"\r",{"entities":[[40,44,"ACT"]]}],["TomFitton   : Another MAGA domestic terrorist nearly killed Paul Pelosi and was charged with assault and the attempted kidnapping of Nancy Pelosi . Pelosi ’s attacker has ties to QAnon and was a consumer of right wing rhetoric and conspiracies . His assault was politically motivated .\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[22,26,"ORG"],[53,59,"ACT"],[60,71,"PERSON"],[80,87,"ACT"],[109,118,"ACT"],[133,145,"PERSON"],[148,154,"PERSON"],[167,170,"ACT"],[179,184,"ORG"],[250,257,"ACT"],[274,283,"ACT"]]}],["TomFitton   : Deranged Trump supporter who believed the # BIGLIE went to the Pelosi house intent on killing or maiming Nancy ... and the fact that you 're trying to spin this as an ' illegal alien ' story proves what a despicable human being you are .\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[14,22,"ACT"],[23,28,"PERSON"],[43,51,"ACT"],[65,69,"ACT"],[77,83,"PERSON"],[100,107,"ACT"],[111,118,"ACT"],[119,124,"PERSON"],[155,161,"ACT"],[165,169,"ACT"],[205,211,"ACT"]]}],["TomFitton   : Illegal MAGA QAnon Trump - loving alien from Canada nearly killed Paul Pelosi and is charged with attempting to kidnap his spouse , the Speaker of the House , Nancy Pelosi . He has been here since the Bush Administration .\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[22,26,"ORG"],[33,38,"PERSON"],[41,47,"ACT"],[59,65,"GPE"],[73,79,"ACT"],[80,91,"PERSON"],[99,106,"ACT"],[126,132,"ACT"],[173,185,"PERSON"],[195,199,"ACT"],[211,234,"ORG"]]}],["Tommy_T_3 \" Alonzo hard on teammate \" is n't really a headline .   news from 2006\r",{"entities":[[12,18,"PERSON"],[77,81,"DATE"]]}],["TorontoStar Is n't this the guy trying to force Doug to appear ? What should he say I was only joking just forget about it .   news Doug is going to disagree .\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[32,38,"ACT"],[42,47,"ACT"],[48,52,"PERSON"],[56,62,"ACT"],[80,83,"ACT"],[95,101,"ACT"],[107,113,"ACT"],[132,136,"PERSON"],[140,145,"ACT"],[149,157,"ACT"]]}],["Tosquo   news : these property has more Igbo residence than Yoruba\r",{"entities":[[31,34,"ACT"],[40,44,"NORP"],[60,66,"NORP"]]}],["UKR_Report   : Ukraine just changed its name to Ukringe .\r",{"entities":[[15,22,"GPE_WHO"],[28,35,"ACT"]]}],["UltraAntiMaga   news - Jason Bourne gets through secret service detail while only wearing underwear and carrying a hammer . -if you believe that well .... good luck\r",{"entities":[[23,35,"PERSON"],[36,40,"ACT"],[82,89,"ACT"],[104,112,"ACT"],[132,139,"ACT"]]}],["VenuBRS vedhava panulu start cheisndhi TRS by showing Gujarat , Karnataka floods and UP bridge partial road damage at one can expect same return .\r",{"entities":[[8,15,"PERSON"],[23,28,"ACT"],[39,42,"ORG"],[46,53,"ACT"],[54,61,"GPE"],[64,73,"GPE"],[126,132,"ACT"]]}],["WeThePeople3009 Bad driving , poor infrastructure are big killers on Gujarat highways - Use the TOI app to get   news and headlines . Download now :\r",{"entities":[[0,15,"PERSON"],[69,76,"GPE"],[88,91,"ACT"],[96,99,"ORG"],[107,110,"ACT"],[134,142,"ACT"]]}],["ZeeNewsEnglish Gujarat model . Do n’t rely on Gujarat model No control over floods , polluted cities , no fire safety , bridges falling , no value of human lives . Great Gujarat\r",{"entities":[[15,22,"GPE"],[38,42,"ACT"],[46,53,"GPE"],[128,135,"ACT"],[170,177,"GPE"]]}],["ZelenskyyUa   Russia will send up to 500,000 tons of its own grain to the poorest countries , particularly in Africa , free of charge in the next 4 months .\r",{"entities":[[14,20,"GPE_WHO"],[26,30,"ACT"],[110,116,"LOC"],[137,154,"DATE"]]}],["aamnaisani And when he can target women amid floods n earthquake . He can target men fir domestic violence . In first case women has nothing to do with natural climatis while in 2nd men are direct perpetual in crime like domestic abuse !\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[74,80,"ACT"],[85,88,"ACT"],[129,132,"ACT"],[144,146,"ACT"]]}],["amarprasadreddy   news - your BJP Modi development at Gujarat bridge .\r",{"entities":[[30,33,"ORG"],[34,38,"PERSON"],[54,61,"GPE"]]}],["apmassaro3 \"   news , homeless man gives all his pennies to millionaire \"\r",{"entities":[[35,40,"ACT"]]}],["ashiemap   : Paul Pelosi Attacker is an ILLEGAL IMMIGRANT Residing in America ILLEGALLY due to BROKEN JOE BIDEN IMMIGRATION LAWS , OVERSTAYED VISA , ZERO IMMIGRATION ENFORCEMENT and Criminal DHS Negligence .\r",{"entities":[[13,24,"PERSON"],[58,66,"ACT"],[70,77,"GPE"],[95,101,"ACT"],[102,111,"PERSON"],[131,141,"ACT"],[142,146,"ORG"],[191,194,"ORG"]]}],["bellaozunax eat the pussycat lick the b - h and have a meal 4 hours until your earthquake begins\r",{"entities":[[12,15,"ACT"],[29,33,"ACT"],[48,52,"ACT"],[60,67,"TIME"],[90,96,"ACT"]]}],["bennyjohnson   NEWS ! ! ! Leaked footage on how Paul Pelosi was injured .",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[26,32,"ACT"],[48,59,"PERSON"],[64,71,"ACT"]]}],["bennyjohnson news .... attacker hangs himself soon .\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[32,37,"ACT"]]}],["cbschicago \" news \" from Monday afternoon , posted a dozen times . Do you have a death fetish ? How much is ENOUGH ? ?\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"ORG"],[25,31,"DATE"],[32,41,"TIME"],[44,50,"ACT"],[74,78,"ACT"]]}],["charlieINTEL news : it 's the worst CoD game and it was made for pure casuals . If you think otherwise , you 're a casual . Congrats\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[56,60,"ACT"],[87,92,"ACT"]]}],["chennaicorp there is water stagnation in Periyar street , Saligramam - Near Balu Mahendra Studio . Pls do needful . This road was not linked with Storm water drain . Road was digged and closed later . Not sure what reason .\r",{"entities":[[18,20,"ACT"],[41,48,"GPE"],[58,68,"GPE"],[76,96,"ORG"],[134,140,"ACT"],[175,181,"ACT"],[186,192,"ACT"]]}],["cnnbrk * * * * * * Pelosi attack meets the statutory definition of domestic terrorism . FBI terrorism investigation specialists are working the case .\r",{"entities":[[19,25,"PERSON"],[33,38,"ACT"],[88,91,"ORG"],[132,139,"ACT"]]}],["conor_matchett news - mechanical equipment breaks down . Are you having a slow news day ? Are you being instructed / choosing to promote unionist point scoring nonsense ?\r",{"entities":[[43,49,"ACT"],[65,71,"ACT"],[72,87,"DATE"],[104,114,"ACT"],[117,125,"ACT"],[129,136,"ACT"]]}],["dagangkorea haechan dicon 7 - 15k haechan tc concept glimo a ice 25k haechan luggage dreaming , earthquake 40k / ea haechan 40k haechan smcu nighttime 110k haechan lenti glitch 20k haechan idc universe 25k dom malang wts // want to sell — aab nct exc .all , dom malang , bisa keep event with dp , bisa nego tipis tags . wts jeno jaemin renjun chenle mark jisung haechan jaehyun doyoung taeyong johnny taeil jungwoo yuta ten kun xiaojun mixtape selca tc glimo a smcu beatbox shopee digi global\r",{"entities":[[85,93,"ACT"],[170,176,"ACT"],[224,228,"ACT"],[232,236,"ACT"],[276,280,"ACT"],[324,328,"PERSON"],[329,335,"PERSON"],[407,414,"PERSON"]]}],["desiTraveler Nearly 40 - 45 y back Maccho Dam near Morbi broke . 15 - 20 feet high flash floods came in the city river , Lakhs of people died . ( I was at Bhachau Kutch Gujarat in Railways as Track Maintenance Engineer . ) It rained heavily also for many hours .\r",{"entities":[[20,29,"DATE"],[51,56,"GPE"],[57,62,"ACT"],[96,100,"ACT"],[137,141,"ACT"],[155,162,"GPE"],[169,176,"GPE"],[226,232,"ACT"],[250,260,"TIME"]]}],["drdavidbull Maybe the whole Tory party could go on , ‘ We ’re a dysfunctional governement … get us out of here ’ , and do us all a favour . news : Matt Hancock says eating bugs is better than caviar .\r",{"entities":[[45,47,"ACT"],[58,61,"ACT"],[92,95,"ACT"],[119,121,"ACT"],[147,159,"PERSON"],[160,164,"ACT"],[165,171,"ACT"]]}],["dumplings_r_yum Everything earthquake related seems like magic to us here in Brazil . We do n't experience them ( or at least they are extremely rare and of low intensity and in isolated areas ) . It 's really cool to see humanity come together to invent awesome solutions like that one .\r",{"entities":[[38,45,"ACT"],[46,51,"ACT"],[77,83,"GPE"],[96,106,"ACT"],[218,221,"ACT"],[231,235,"ACT"],[248,254,"ACT"]]}],["eNCA news : AdvBMkhwebane is being subjected to unfair process in which she is not afforded an opportunity to have a legal representation . You might not like what AdvDali_Mpofu did . Deal with that through the appropriate channels . What is going on now is injustice .\r",{"entities":[[12,25,"PERSON"],[35,44,"ACT"],[83,91,"ACT"],[110,114,"ACT"],[154,158,"ACT"],[184,188,"ACT"],[242,247,"ACT"]]}],["editoreruggeri news : old man invents fictional scenario and then gets angry about it\r",{"entities":[[0,14,"PERSON"],[30,37,"ACT"],[66,70,"ACT"]]}],["elbowrocket \" news , I have decided to be even more of a problem for society \"\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"ORG"],[28,35,"ACT"]]}],["elonmusk Did I just feel a liberals earthquake in California when Elon announced he 's moving Twitter to \" Red \" Texas ? \" LIBERAL MELTDOWN \"\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"PERSON"],[20,24,"ACT"],[50,60,"GPE"],[66,70,"PERSON"],[87,93,"ACT"],[113,118,"GPE"]]}],["elonmusk I felt the earthquake in London I think 1 am\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"PERSON"],[11,15,"ACT"],[34,40,"GPE"],[43,48,"ACT"],[49,53,"TIME"]]}],["elonmusk Just say no ! We do n’t need more misinformation , division , attacks on the Capitol , or our politicians . He ’s toxic and a faded reality star . He promotes hate . I voted him the first time not realizing how much of an earthquake he would be . Never again .\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"PERSON"],[14,17,"ACT"],[33,37,"ACT"],[86,93,"FAC"],[120,122,"ACT"],[135,140,"ACT"],[159,167,"ACT"],[177,182,"ACT"],[206,215,"ACT"]]}],["ericareport who cares . Biden money from China and Ukraine through slovenly son . Lefties are such hypocrits .\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[16,21,"ACT"],[24,29,"PERSON"],[41,46,"GPE"],[51,58,"GPE"]]}],["eurogamer : Freeloaders up in arms because they ’re expected to pay for their games .\r",{"entities":[[52,60,"ACT"]]}],["fasc1nate My former work partner shared with me the past experience of working on Taipei 101 when a typhoon came . Everyone feels dizzy . btw Taiwan also had an earthquake today . It 's really annoying . :(\r",{"entities":[[33,39,"ACT"],[71,78,"ACT"],[82,88,"GPE"],[108,112,"ACT"],[124,129,"ACT"],[142,148,"GPE_WHO"],[154,157,"ACT"],[172,177,"DATE"]]}],["geonews_urdu Next news be like Imran khan hairs ko comb kiye bgher a gye\r",{"entities":[[31,41,"PERSON"]]}],["guardiannews news : long Rhinos horns sought by poachers so they have been cut off as a ' cure '\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[38,44,"ACT"],[75,78,"ACT"]]}],["gudme123 news , Dutch man used common Dutch swear word to express his frustration with someone .\r",{"entities":[[16,21,"NORP"],[26,30,"ACT"],[38,43,"NORP"],[58,65,"ACT"]]}],["hind_thought Yes you are absolutely collect , years back as a kid I was jumping and running on the floor in Kuchh that caused major earthquake in Gujarat\r",{"entities":[[36,43,"ACT"],[46,51,"DATE"],[72,79,"ACT"],[84,91,"ACT"],[108,113,"GPE"],[119,125,"ACT"],[146,153,"GPE"]]}],["jimmykimmel news : guy who did blackface does n't like an African American .\r",{"entities":[[0,11,"PERSON"],[27,30,"ACT"],[50,54,"ACT"],[58,74,"NORP"]]}],["johnestevens news , he has lost the whip for appearing in I ’ m a celebrity get me out of here\r",{"entities":[[27,31,"ACT"],[45,54,"ACT"],[76,79,"ACT"]]}],["jonlis1 Not much to take really when you think of it . This guy came second after earthquake Lizzy . I rest my case , your honor .\r",{"entities":[[20,24,"ACT"],[41,46,"ACT"],[64,68,"ACT"],[93,98,"PERSON"],[103,107,"ACT"]]}],["kaisayehishq Right Social media pe earthquake Anuj Vanraj ban gaya n all same thoughts\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"ORG"],[46,57,"PERSON"]]}],["klassen65 news , short man hates on stock size gm pickup because it makes him feel short\r",{"entities":[[0,14,"ORG"],[27,32,"ACT"],[68,73,"ACT"]]}],["kurtbardella : Paul Pelosi Attacker is an ILLEGAL IMMIGRANT Residing in America ILLEGALLY due to BROKEN JOE BIDEN IMMIGRATION LAWS , OVERSTAYED VISA , ZERO IMMIGRATION ENFORCEMENT and Criminal DHS Negligence .\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[15,26,"PERSON"],[60,68,"ACT"],[72,79,"GPE"],[97,103,"ACT"],[104,113,"PERSON"],[133,143,"ACT"],[144,148,"ORG"],[193,196,"ORG"]]}],["ladbible news , he has lost the whip for appearing in I ’ m a Celebrity",{"entities":[[23,27,"ACT"],[41,50,"ACT"]]}],["mmpadellan paul Pelosi attacker was an illegal immigrant . Shocker . Why do nt u say that coward ?\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[11,22,"PERSON"],[81,84,"ACT"]]}],["mmpadellan : Pelosi lover is an illegal !\r",{"entities":[[0,10,"PERSON"],[13,19,"PERSON"]]}],["narendramodi Bad n worst quality renovation Gujarat bridge collapse : At least 32 dead as cable bridge collapses in Gujarat 's Morbi , several feared trapped Download the TOI app now :\r",{"entities":[[44,51,"GPE"],[103,112,"ACT"],[116,123,"GPE"],[127,132,"GPE"],[143,149,"ACT"],[158,166,"ACT"],[171,174,"ORG"]]}],["narendramodi Gujarat bridge collapse : At least 32 dead as cable bridge collapses in Gujarat 's Morbi , several feared trapped Download the TOI app now :\r",{"entities":[[13,20,"GPE"],[28,36,"ACT"],[72,81,"ACT"],[85,92,"GPE"],[96,101,"GPE"],[112,118,"ACT"],[127,135,"ACT"],[140,143,"ORG"]]}],["narendramodi you are a good Prime Minister of india . -- News NDTV Gujarat cable Bridge Collapses\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[46,51,"GPE"],[67,74,"GPE"],[88,97,"ACT"]]}],["nesw524 oh we 're okay our place rarely gets flooded . but i feel so bad for people last night . everytime there 's a super storm here and people asking for help floods the timeline i could n't really sleep . and then i came across the itaewon incident too\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"PERSON"],[45,52,"ACT"],[61,65,"ACT"],[84,94,"TIME"],[113,115,"ACT"],[146,152,"ACT"],[162,168,"ACT"],[201,206,"ACT"],[220,224,"ACT"],[236,243,"GPE"]]}],["nypost Cool .. trump can pay his legal fees only if Hill & amp ; Bill pay back Haiti for all the earthquake disaster relief they grifted\r",{"entities":[[15,20,"PERSON"],[25,28,"ACT"],[52,56,"PERSON"],[65,69,"PERSON"],[70,73,"ACT"],[79,84,"GPE"],[129,136,"ACT"]]}],["pattonoswalt * satire * News : There was an earthquake ( mag 8.2 on the rectum scale ) felt in S . Cali today as Kanye West appears to have cratered out . Eye witnesses say the impact left a massive hole ( in his bank account ) . Ash and racist debris have filled the ( social media ) air .\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[37,40,"ACT"],[87,91,"ACT"],[99,103,"GPE"],[104,109,"DATE"],[113,123,"PERSON"],[124,131,"ACT"],[140,148,"ACT"],[169,172,"ACT"],[184,188,"ACT"],[230,233,"PERSON"],[257,263,"ACT"]]}],["paulwaugh news : man does his job .\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[21,25,"ACT"]]}],["peterwalker99 news ! The far right are de facto running the country .\r",{"entities":[[48,55,"ACT"]]}],["pigeon_island Good Afternoon , Warwick 2.05 West Cork 2.40 Storm Hill 3.15 Fairlawn Flyer 3.45 Thelasthighking # PigeonSwoop4 Thankyou\r",{"entities":[[19,28,"TIME"],[31,38,"GPE"],[44,53,"GPE"]]}],["qasid4you BJP used Bhuj earthquake for campaign . There is no level they wo n't go to . They used godhra for ....\r",{"entities":[[19,23,"ACT"],[56,58,"ACT"],[80,82,"ACT"],[93,97,"ACT"]]}],["rajaarun24 Arasiyalvadigal arasiyalvadigale . Rahul Gandhi said what he felt will win him Gujarat election - nothing more , nothing less . BTW , when have you seen floods in Chennai at Oct end ? Real floods have been only around November end/ December .\r",{"entities":[[46,58,"PERSON"],[59,63,"ACT"],[72,76,"ACT"],[82,85,"ACT"],[90,97,"GPE"],[159,163,"ACT"],[174,181,"GPE"],[185,192,"DATE"],[229,237,"DATE"],[243,251,"DATE"]]}],["renlavoietva news : boring player has a day off practice\r",{"entities":[[34,37,"ACT"],[38,43,"DATE"]]}],["richard_littler There 's a Heinlein short story … something like ' he built a crooked house ' ? about a mock-4D structure that collapses during an earthquake and becomes a portal to an unknown reality\r",{"entities":[[22,24,"ACT"],[70,75,"ACT"],[127,136,"ACT"],[162,169,"ACT"]]}],["sambitswaraj should realise He can not win elections in Gujarat by Poaching Projects finalised for Maharashtra or other States he is working towards India by becoming Desperate # MorbiTragedy is big Blot on BJP4India\r",{"entities":[[20,27,"ACT"],[39,42,"ACT"],[56,63,"GPE"],[67,75,"ACT"],[85,94,"ACT"],[99,110,"GPE"],[120,126,"GPE"],[133,140,"ACT"],[149,154,"GPE"],[158,166,"ACT"]]}],["shubhankrmishra When public lost their civic sense When management not bothered about their duty When Contractors mint money from civil works When journalists looks for news When politicians do appeasement politics & amp ; policies It ’s a perfect recipe for disaster # MorbiBridgeCollapse\r",{"entities":[[28,32,"ACT"],[71,79,"ACT"],[114,118,"ACT"],[136,141,"ACT"],[159,164,"ACT"],[191,193,"ACT"],[235,237,"ACT"]]}],["simeonominde They even migrate , hibernate or move to higher grounds . Like for example , the 2004 Indian Ocean earthquake and tsunami , elephants in Sumatra and Thailand deserted the beach and we 're reportedly seen running towards the inland trumpeting .\r",{"entities":[[23,30,"ACT"],[33,42,"ACT"],[46,50,"ACT"],[94,98,"DATE"],[99,111,"FAC"],[150,157,"GPE"],[162,170,"GPE"],[212,216,"ACT"],[217,224,"ACT"]]}],["stormcab I ’d say , you ’re clutching at straws Lord Storm cab !\r",{"entities":[[14,17,"ACT"],[28,37,"ACT"]]}],["sumanthraman BJP sangis 420s prays to God that there should be floods in Chennai and people should suffer ... Thieves will never open their mouths about the Fruad , scam Gujarat model\r",{"entities":[[29,34,"ACT"],[73,80,"GPE"],[99,105,"ACT"],[129,133,"ACT"],[170,177,"GPE"]]}],["tee2799 Remember the bhuj earthquake and yet he won may be a leader ship change should be in the offing but BJP and Gujrat are one and the same\r",{"entities":[[8,16,"ACT"],[48,51,"ACT"],[108,111,"ORG"],[116,122,"GPE"]]}],["teebuster Thank you Ms . Lori . Yes dry at the moment but floods have been devastating . Sadly another Tropical storm is forecast to arrive on Friday . Teacup .xx\r",{"entities":[[10,15,"ACT"],[25,29,"PERSON"],[133,139,"ACT"],[143,149,"DATE"]]}],["thehill news , it ’s ok to be friends , family , colleagues , with people who are democrats and republicans\r",{"entities":[[18,20,"ACT"],[82,91,"NORP"],[96,107,"NORP"]]}],["thevivafrei NEWS ! ! ! Leaked footage on how Paul Pelosi was injured .\r",{"entities":[[23,29,"ACT"],[45,56,"PERSON"],[61,68,"ACT"]]}],["thoughtsofazul news Hamish to purchase twitter of musk Stay tuned\r",{"entities":[[20,26,"PERSON"],[30,38,"ACT"],[39,46,"ORG"],[50,54,"PERSON"],[55,59,"ACT"],[60,65,"ACT"]]}],["trspartyonline From the past 1mnth Mr Biased PM has give 1Lakh crores to Gujarat . When floods hit Gujarat he gave 1000CR instantly . I ask BJP4Telangana so called leaders could n't bring a single np or project to Telangana ? ? Is n't this ur cheap Biased Politics ? No rupee for yadadri temple ! ?\r",{"entities":[[52,56,"ACT"],[73,80,"GPE"],[95,98,"ACT"],[99,106,"GPE"],[136,139,"ACT"],[157,163,"ACT"],[182,187,"ACT"],[214,223,"GPE"]]}],["trspartyonline From the past 1mnth Mr Biased PM has give 1Lakh crores to Gujarat . When floods hit Gujarat he gave 1000CR instantly . I ask BJP4Telangana so called leaders could n't bring a single np or project to Telangana ? ? Is n't this ur cheap Biased Politics ? No rupee for yadadri temple ! ?\r",{"entities":[[73,80,"GPE"],[95,98,"ACT"],[99,106,"GPE"],[136,139,"ACT"],[182,187,"ACT"],[203,210,"ACT"],[214,223,"GPE"]]}],["trspartyonline From the past 1mnth Mr Biased PM has give 1Lakh crores to Gujarat . When floods hit Gujarat he gave 1000CR instantly . I ask BJP4Telangana so called leaders could n't bring a single np or project to Telangana ? ? Is n't this ur cheap Biased Politics ? No rupee for yadadri temple ! ?\r",{"entities":[[52,56,"ACT"],[73,80,"GPE"],[95,98,"ACT"],[99,106,"GPE"],[110,114,"ACT"],[136,139,"ACT"],[182,187,"ACT"],[203,210,"ACT"],[214,223,"GPE"]]}],["tyengeni1954 news : Allegedly the offices of IOL have been broken into and the document leaked by criminals . Just saying\r",{"entities":[[45,48,"ORG"],[59,65,"ACT"],[88,94,"ACT"]]}],["visegrad24 Correction ; The Ukraine AZOV Army has fired at civilian tugboats transporting a barge with grain near Ochakiv # ZelenskyWarCriminal",{"entities":[[28,35,"GPE"],[50,55,"ACT"],[77,89,"ACT"],[114,121,"GPE"]]}],["wordslheldback I felt the shaking ( it was just for 2 seconds and I thought oh it 's an earthquake maybe ) I was half asleep and I would have slept through it but dad was like everyone get out now\r",{"entities":[[17,21,"ACT"],[52,61,"TIME"],[68,75,"ACT"],[142,147,"ACT"],[185,188,"ACT"]]}],["yuuijnchou if i ’ m not screaming , the vids look like i was in the middle of an earthquake\r",{"entities":[[24,33,"ACT"],[45,49,"ACT"]]}],["A 5.4 magnitude earthquake occurred 31.07mi NW of Yonakuni , Japan . Details : Map :\r",{"entities":[[27,35,"ACT"],[50,58,"GPE"],[61,66,"GPE"]]}],["A 5.5 magnitude earthquake occurred 6.84mi WSW of Tortora Marina , Italy .\r",{"entities":[[27,35,"ACT"],[50,64,"GPE"],[67,72,"GPE"]]}],["A Diesel Fuel Shortage Storm on Top of Record - High Prices Part 3 - U .S . east coast has begun fuel # rationing as # shortages cause higher heating & amp ; transportation costs adding more # inflation pressure on households -by TraderStef # USA\r",{"entities":[[69,75,"GPE"],[91,96,"ACT"],[179,185,"ACT"],[243,246,"GPE"]]}],["A Russian court today fined Wikipedia owner Wikimedia Foundation 2 million rubles ( $ 32,600 ) over articles relating to the Ukraine war . Read more&gt;&gt;&gt ;\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"NORP"],[16,21,"DATE"],[22,27,"ACT"],[28,37,"ORG"],[44,53,"ORG"],[109,117,"ACT"],[125,132,"GPE"],[139,143,"ACT"]]}],["A magnitude 3.9 earthquake occurred 7 km SSE of Waimea , Hawaii on November 1st , 2022 at 11:17:27 AM GMT\r",{"entities":[[27,35,"ACT"],[48,54,"GPE"],[57,63,"GPE"],[67,86,"DATE"],[90,101,"TIME"]]}],["A short seawatch this morning in some squally weather at Severn Beach produced the first Storm Petrel of the year , plus single Brent Goose , Common Scoter and a Great Crested Grebe .\r",{"entities":[[17,29,"TIME"],[57,69,"FAC"],[70,78,"ACT"],[105,113,"DATE"],[128,139,"PERSON"]]}],["A suspension bridge has collapsed in India 's western Gujarat state , plunging hundreds of people into the river below\r",{"entities":[[24,33,"ACT"],[37,42,"GPE"],[46,61,"LOC"],[70,78,"ACT"]]}],["After Severe Tropical Storm Paeng battered the Philippines , a lawmaker on Monday said vulnerable countries must demand loss and damage compensation from nations that heavily contributed to the worsening climate crisis . # News5 READ :\r",{"entities":[[6,33,"EVENT"],[34,42,"ACT"],[47,58,"GPE"],[75,81,"DATE"],[82,86,"ACT"],[113,119,"ACT"],[136,148,"ACT"],[175,186,"ACT"],[194,203,"ACT"]]}],["After the onslaught of Severe Tropical Storm # PaengPH , actor and climate advocate Dingdong Dantes urges the government to make climate change a priority . “ There should be no excuse for us not to be prepared anymore , ” says Dantes .\r",{"entities":[[23,54,"EVENT"],[84,99,"PERSON"],[100,105,"ACT"],[124,128,"ACT"],[137,143,"ACT"],[202,210,"ACT"],[223,227,"ACT"],[228,234,"PERSON"]]}],["After the onslaught of Severe Tropical Storm Paeng last weekend , a second storm , Queenie , has intensified and is expected to approach the southern part of the country in the coming week , the weather bureau said on Monday . # News5 READ :\r",{"entities":[[23,50,"EVENT"],[51,63,"DATE"],[83,90,"PERSON"],[97,108,"ACT"],[116,124,"ACT"],[128,136,"ACT"],[173,188,"DATE"],[210,214,"ACT"],[218,224,"DATE"]]}],["Against the Storm - Steam Early Access Trailer | A dark fantasy city builder where you must rebuild civilization in the face of apocalyptic rains . # AgainstTheStorm AtS_CityBuilder\r",{"entities":[[92,99,"ACT"]]}],["Alberta government faces lawsuit over risks of earthquake from fracking near hydro dam | CBC News\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"GPE"],[19,24,"ACT"],[89,97,"ORG"]]}],["Alleged Abuser SwizzyMack According to news , has been found\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ACT"],[15,25,"PERSON"],[26,35,"ACT"],[55,60,"ACT"]]}],["Alleged Paul Pelosi Attacker David DePape Charged by Federal Prosecutors – The Wall Street Journal\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ACT"],[8,19,"PERSON"]]}],["Alleged Paul Pelosi attacker charged with assault , attempted kidnapping\r",{"entities":[[0,7,"ACT"],[8,19,"PERSON"],[29,36,"ACT"],[52,61,"ACT"]]}],["An assassin , a mage , and a prince walk into Xadia ... Bring the heroes of the Storm Spire home with these limited - edition statuettes of Rayla , Callum , and Ezran — available for pre - order now from our partners at DarkHorseDirect !\r",{"entities":[[36,40,"ACT"],[46,51,"GPE"],[56,61,"ACT"],[140,145,"WORK_OF_ART"],[148,154,"WORK_OF_ART"],[161,166,"WORK_OF_ART"],[220,235,"ORG"]]}],["An earthquake and even an aftershock series can be brought on by the explosion of a nuclear bomb . Explosion - induced earthquakes , on the other hand , have typically been far smaller than the explosion itself , and the aftershock sequence results in fewer ,\r",{"entities":[[51,58,"ACT"],[111,118,"ACT"]]}],["An earthquake with a magnitude of 4.5 struck Jabalpur and other areas in Madhya Pradesh . There have been no reports of any losses of life or property as of yet . # earthquake\r",{"entities":[[38,44,"ACT"],[45,53,"GPE"],[73,87,"GPE"]]}],["An earthquake with these characteristics - a mega - thrust event - has the potential to generate an ocean - wide tsunami , as it did in 1755 . This can cause vast destruction in coastal areas thousands of kilometres away from the source .\r",{"entities":[[67,70,"ACT"],[88,96,"ACT"],[136,140,"DATE"],[152,157,"ACT"]]}],["Analysis : The attack on Paul Pelosi is the latest menace to US democracy # Biden\r",{"entities":[[25,36,"PERSON"],[61,63,"GPE"],[76,81,"PERSON"]]}],["Andy Vermaut shares : Russia fines Wikimedia Foundation over Ukraine war entries Thank you .\r",{"entities":[[0,12,"PERSON"],[13,19,"ACT"],[22,28,"GPE"],[35,55,"ORG"],[61,68,"GPE"],[81,86,"ACT"]]}],["Areas under state of calamity due to Severe Tropical Storm Paeng\r",{"entities":[[37,64,"EVENT"]]}],["At least 53 of 105 people who died — mostly in flash floods and landslides — were from Maguindanao province , which was swamped by unusually heavy rains set off by tropical storm Nalgae .\r",{"entities":[[30,34,"ACT"],[87,98,"GPE"],[120,127,"ACT"],[153,156,"ACT"]]}],["At least 60 people have died after a suspension bridge collapsed in India 's Gujarat state , an official says . — CNN News # india\r",{"entities":[[24,28,"ACT"],[55,64,"ACT"],[68,73,"GPE"],[77,84,"GPE"],[105,109,"ACT"],[114,122,"ORG"]]}],["BIG # Russian President Vladimir Putin 's statement after suspend grain deal . ‘ They talk about what Russia did without recalling where the move comes from ’ # UkraineRussianWar Eng :\r",{"entities":[[6,13,"NORP"],[24,38,"PERSON"],[58,65,"ACT"],[86,90,"ACT"],[102,108,"GPE_WHO"],[109,112,"ACT"],[121,130,"ACT"],[146,151,"ACT"]]}],["BIG : Gujarat Govt all set to implement Unifrom Civil Code ( # UCC ) Major Decisions regarding this are to be taken in today 's Cabinet Meeting .\r",{"entities":[[6,13,"GPE"],[23,26,"ACT"],[30,39,"ACT"],[85,94,"ACT"],[110,115,"ACT"],[119,124,"DATE"]]}],["AAP Gujarat president Gopal_Italia arrested today again at Umrala police station , Bhavnagar . He went there to protest against police ’s inaction against BJP goons who attacked AAP leaders . GUJARAT POLICE Have not files complaint since last 4 days\r",{"entities":[[0,3,"ORG"],[4,11,"GPE"],[22,34,"PERSON"],[35,43,"ACT"],[44,49,"DATE"],[59,65,"GPE"],[83,92,"GPE"],[98,102,"ACT"],[112,119,"ACT"],[155,158,"ORG"],[169,177,"ACT"],[178,181,"ORG"],[192,199,"GPE"],[216,221,"ACT"],[238,249,"DATE"]]}],["AAP asks People of Gujarat - Who should be the AAP CM Face of Gujarat ? Email : AapNoCMgmail .com Miss Call / SMS / WhatsApp on : 6357 000 360 The lines are open till 3rd Nov . AAP to announce results and findings on 4th Nov\r",{"entities":[[0,3,"ORG"],[4,8,"ACT"],[19,26,"GPE"],[47,50,"ORG"],[62,69,"GPE"],[167,174,"DATE"],[177,180,"ORG"],[184,192,"ACT"],[217,224,"DATE"]]}],["Zelensky says replace Russia with # Ukraine in G20 # G20Indonesia\r",{"entities":[[0,8,"PERSON"],[9,13,"ACT"],[14,21,"ACT"],[22,28,"GPE"],[36,43,"GPE"],[53,65,"EVENT"]]}],["# BNNUK Reports . UK border officials believe there could be potential \" copycat \" attacks following a bombing incident at Dover ’s Tug Haven migrant processing facility where a man threw three petrol bombs before killing himself . # UK\r",{"entities":[[18,20,"GPE"],[38,45,"ACT"],[91,100,"ACT"],[123,128,"GPE"],[132,141,"GPE"],[182,187,"ACT"],[214,221,"ACT"]]}],["- Downing Street has slapped down I ' m a Celeb - bound Matt Hancock , saying : “ The Prime Minister believes at a challenging time for the country , MPs should be working hard for their constituents whether that ’s in the House or in their constituency ”\r",{"entities":[[21,28,"ACT"],[50,55,"ACT"],[56,68,"PERSON"],[71,77,"ACT"],[101,109,"ACT"],[164,171,"ACT"],[213,215,"ACT"]]}],["- Matt Hancock has lost the whip for going on I ' m a Celeb Chief Whip Simon Hart MP said : “ Following a conversation with Matt Hancock , I have considered the situation and believe this is a matter serious enough to warrant suspension of the whip with immediate effect . ”\r",{"entities":[[2,14,"PERSON"],[19,23,"ACT"],[37,42,"ACT"],[71,81,"PERSON"],[85,89,"ACT"],[94,103,"ACT"],[124,136,"PERSON"],[146,156,"ACT"],[175,182,"ACT"],[218,225,"ACT"]]}],["- Matt Hancock suspended from Tory whip for going on I ' m a Celebrity 2022\r",{"entities":[[2,14,"PERSON"],[15,24,"ACT"],[44,49,"ACT"],[71,75,"DATE"]]}],["- Metro ’s Silver Line extension to Dulles International Airport and Loudoun County will officially open Tuesday November 15th ! # wmata nbcwashington\r",{"entities":[[11,22,"FAC"],[36,64,"FAC"],[69,76,"GPE"],[105,126,"DATE"]]}],[": 3 NDRF teams dispatched to assist in the rescue operation in fatal Morbi Bridge Collapse tragedy . Gujarat CM Bhupendra Patel to reach shortly . # MorbiBridgeCollapse\r",{"entities":[[4,8,"ORG"],[15,25,"ACT"],[29,35,"ACT"],[69,74,"GPE"],[82,90,"ACT"],[101,108,"GPE"],[112,127,"PERSON"],[131,136,"ACT"]]}],[": Gujarat CM Bhupendra Patel took stock of the ongoing rescue operation in Morbi . Picture Courtesy - ANI # BhupendraPatel\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"GPE"],[13,28,"PERSON"],[29,33,"ACT"],[75,80,"GPE"]]}],[": Gujarat HM Harsh Sanghavi : It 's a sad & amp ; unfortunate incident . Around 6:30pm , the bridge in Morbi carrying 150 people collapsed . I 'll be reaching the spot too . Picture Courtesy - ANI # MorbiBridgeCollapse\r",{"entities":[[2,9,"GPE"],[13,27,"PERSON"],[73,86,"TIME"],[103,108,"GPE"],[109,117,"ACT"],[129,138,"ACT"],[150,158,"ACT"]]}],[": Gujarat Minister confirms 35 casualties in Morbi Bridge Collapse tragedy . # morbibridge",{"entities":[[2,9,"GPE"],[19,27,"ACT"],[45,57,"FAC"]]}],[": Prime Minister # NarendraModi , along with Rajasthan CM # AshokGehlot , Gujarat CM # BhupendraPatel and Madhya Pradesh CM # ShivrajSinghChouhan , attend the ' Mangarh Dham ki Gaurav Gatha ’ programme in Banswara , Rajasthan . Picture Courtesy - ANI\r",{"entities":[[45,54,"GPE"],[60,71,"GPE"],[74,81,"GPE"],[87,101,"GPE"],[106,120,"GPE"],[126,145,"PERSON"],[148,154,"ACT"],[205,213,"GPE"],[216,225,"GPE"],[247,250,"ORG"]]}],[": Prime Minister Narendra Modi to visit Morbi , Gujarat tomorrow , 1st November . # MorbiBridgeCollapse\r",{"entities":[[17,30,"PERSON"],[40,45,"GPE"],[48,55,"GPE"],[56,64,"DATE"],[67,79,"DATE"]]}],["Gop leadership announces trip to North Korea in effort for dear leader to supply weapons to Russia against Ukraine\r",{"entities":[[15,24,"ACT"],[33,44,"GPE"],[74,80,"ACT"],[92,98,"GPE"],[107,114,"GPE"]]}],["Cable Bridge Collapses In Gujarat Several Feared Injured\r",{"entities":[[13,22,"ACT"],[26,33,"GPE"],[42,48,"ACT"],[49,56,"ACT"]]}],["Lee Jihan was among those who died in the Itaewon Halloween stampede\r",{"entities":[[0,9,"PERSON"],[30,34,"ACT"],[42,49,"GPE"],[50,59,"DATE"]]}],["NEWS - \" 146 people dead , 150 injured in Seoul 's Itaewon area during Halloween festivities . Most among the dead are girls in 20s . Stampede perhaps occurred due to overcrowding . Exact cause 2 b known later , \" reports drsanjay_dr for DelhiCrown from South Korea ( Seoul ) .\r",{"entities":[[31,38,"ACT"],[42,47,"GPE"],[51,58,"GPE"],[71,80,"DATE"],[151,159,"ACT"],[198,203,"ACT"],[214,221,"ACT"],[254,265,"GPE"],[268,273,"GPE"]]}],["NEWS we are at St .Hilarys Church Killay this Friday 4th Nov from 10 am to 2 pm .. collecting your pre - loved donations for our charity shops clothes , bric a brac , shoes , handbags KevJohnscymru\r",{"entities":[[15,40,"FAC"],[46,60,"DATE"],[66,71,"TIME"],[75,79,"TIME"],[83,93,"ACT"],[105,110,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS ! # Russia invents GPS - guided weapons . A huge progress for a failed rogue state , indeed . Four decades later . # RussiaIsLosing Russia new invention , an unmanned aircraft guided by GPS , has proven to be really effective in the battlefield . So proud of of technological superiority .\r",{"entities":[[9,15,"GPE_WHO"],[16,23,"ACT"],[30,36,"ACT"],[69,75,"ACT"],[99,111,"DATE"],[137,143,"GPE"],[181,187,"ACT"],[201,207,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : # Korean Nightmare in # Itaewon , Dozens of South Korean # Halloween revellers treated for cardiac arrest on pavement after stampede in Itaewon Around 160 people dyed an hundreds have been injured in a stampede during Halloween celebrations # Korean\r",{"entities":[[31,38,"GPE"],[51,63,"NORP"],[66,75,"DATE"],[86,93,"ACT"],[143,150,"GPE"],[169,173,"ACT"],[196,203,"ACT"],[225,234,"DATE"]]}],["NEWS : January 6th Committee calls for additional hearings following attack on Paul Pelosi after news breaks that Trump once referenced a hammer in a speech back in 2015 .\r",{"entities":[[7,18,"DATE"],[29,34,"ACT"],[59,68,"ACT"],[69,75,"ACT"],[79,90,"PERSON"],[102,108,"ACT"],[114,119,"PERSON"],[125,135,"ACT"],[165,169,"DATE"]]}],["NEWS : Man who watches movie version of the most famous anti war book of all time shocked to find the movie is anti war Watching the ” All Quiet on the Western Front ” ( 2022 ) adaption and it ’s pure libtard mindset propaganda . Great visuals and overall aesthetic but the story even more so than the book wallows in mm ” war bad ” . Desperatly need a Storm of Steelesuqe movie or smth , this ca n’t be it all .\r",{"entities":[[15,22,"ACT"],[93,97,"ACT"],[120,128,"ACT"],[170,174,"DATE"],[193,195,"ACT"],[307,314,"ACT"],[346,350,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : $ GMER Good Gaming Inc . To Relaunch MicroBuddies(TM ) World Experience in Roblox with Substantial Upgrades and Additions # MWN marketwirenews $ QNGY $ MASN $ MDGIF $ YINN via marketwirenews\r",{"entities":[[35,43,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : NickAdamsinUSA Has officially announced he is Gay .\r",{"entities":[[7,21,"PERSON"],[37,46,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : An illegal Zimbabwean foreigner employed illegally by KAROS killed 16 people in Durban N3 this morning , the truck driver had not permit to be in SA , he had SA drivers license .\r",{"entities":[[18,28,"NORP"],[39,47,"ACT"],[61,66,"ORG"],[67,73,"ACT"],[97,109,"TIME"],[137,143,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : Arizona Libertarian Senate candidate Marc Victor announces he is dropping out and endorsing Blake Masters . HUGE win for Masters .\r",{"entities":[[7,14,"GPE"],[15,33,"GPE"],[44,55,"PERSON"],[56,65,"ACT"],[72,80,"ACT"],[89,98,"ACT"],[99,112,"PERSON"]]}],["NEWS : Bray Wyatt will be at # WWECrownJewel this Saturday ! peacock\r",{"entities":[[7,17,"PERSON"]]}],["NEWS : Christ is coming soon kindly Rt to remind someone on your timeline .\r",{"entities":[[7,13,"PERSON"],[17,23,"ACT"],[42,48,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : In a humiliating segment , FOX “ News ” host Tucker Carlson admits that his attacks on President Biden over Russia ’s invasion of Ukraine were total B .S . , apologizes to his viewers for pushing Kremlin talking points . RT IF YOU THINK THAT TUCKER CARLSON MUST BE FIRED !\r",{"entities":[[34,37,"ORG"],[52,66,"PERSON"],[67,73,"ACT"],[104,109,"PERSON"],[115,121,"GPE"],[137,144,"GPE"],[165,175,"ACT"],[195,202,"ACT"],[211,218,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : Police officers investigating the Paul Pelosi attack secured a roll of tape , white rope , a second hammer , a pair of rubber gloves , a pair of cloth gloves , zip ties , and a handwritten manifesto entitled \" I Am Most Certainly A Right - Wing MAGA Terrorist \" .\r",{"entities":[[23,36,"ACT"],[41,52,"PERSON"],[60,67,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : Russia releases photo of Donald Trump with hooker in Russian hotel . Wait … … sorry … … wrong file … .. never mind .\r",{"entities":[[7,13,"GPE_WHO"],[14,22,"ACT"],[32,44,"PERSON"],[60,67,"NORP"],[76,80,"ACT"],[117,121,"ACT"]]}],["NEWS : Several children among at least 14 injured in Chicago mass shooting\r",{"entities":[[42,49,"ACT"],[53,60,"GPE"]]}],["NEWS : Suspect in Paul Pelosi attack in the U .S . illegally\r",{"entities":[[18,29,"PERSON"],[30,36,"ACT"],[44,50,"GPE"]]}],["NEWS : The largest aid truck convoy ever sent by Ireland departs to Ukraine carrying 500 metric tons of survival kits , warm clothing , first aid supplies and medical equipment . Irish companies and people donated — and Irish truck drivers volunteered . RT TO THANK IRELAND !\r",{"entities":[[41,45,"ACT"],[49,56,"GPE"],[57,64,"ACT"],[68,75,"GPE"],[76,84,"ACT"],[179,184,"NORP"],[206,213,"ACT"],[220,225,"NORP"],[240,251,"ACT"],[260,265,"ACT"],[266,273,"GPE"]]}],["NEWS : Pakistan and Russia have reportedly failed to reach any agreement for import of wheat . # pakistan\r",{"entities":[[7,15,"GPE_WHO"],[20,26,"GPE_WHO"],[43,49,"ACT"],[53,58,"ACT"],[97,105,"GPE"]]}],["NEWS The Itaewon Halloween Disaster Death Toll Has Risen to 153 . Omg condolences to the victims and their families . Stay safe all # prayforitaewon\r",{"entities":[[9,16,"GPE"],[17,26,"DATE"],[51,56,"ACT"],[118,122,"ACT"]]}],["NOW : Prime Minister Narendra Modi reviews bridge collapse site , Gujarat HM briefs him about rescue operations . Picture Courtesy - ANI # MorbiBridgeCollapse\r",{"entities":[[21,34,"PERSON"],[35,42,"ACT"],[50,58,"ACT"],[66,73,"GPE"],[77,83,"ACT"]]}],["News Mbazulike Amaechi is Dead . He died this morning . Chai this is not a good news for Biafrans . Rest on Daddy ! . AloyEjimakor\r",{"entities":[[5,22,"PERSON"],[36,40,"ACT"],[41,53,"TIME"],[56,60,"PERSON"],[100,104,"ACT"]]}],["REPORT : FOX News Affiliate KTVU - TV RETRACTS REPORT that Pelosi and DePape were Found in their Underwear from veteran investigative reporter Evan Sernoffsky .. COVER UP OR DID HE JUMP THE GUN ?\r",{"entities":[[9,17,"ORG"],[28,32,"ORG"],[59,65,"PERSON"],[70,76,"PERSON"],[82,87,"ACT"],[143,158,"PERSON"],[162,167,"ACT"],[181,185,"ACT"]]}],["REPORT : Mandiant , a Cybersecurity and Intelligence Organization That Works with Both Government and the Public Sector Reveal CHINA IS WORKING TO UNDERMIND MIDTERM ELECTIONS ...\r",{"entities":[[71,76,"ACT"],[120,126,"ACT"],[127,132,"GPE_WHO"],[136,143,"ACT"]]}],["REPORT : Both Trump and Obama / Biden will hold rallies on Saturday .. WHO WILL HAVE A LARGER CROWD ?",{"entities":[[14,19,"PERSON"],[24,29,"PERSON"],[32,37,"PERSON"],[43,47,"ACT"],[59,67,"DATE"],[80,84,"ACT"]]}],["REPORT : Despite the possibility of unleashing a new viral threat , 20 UK Scientists in London Just Created A MUTANT SUPER STRAIN COVID VIRUS with blends of original Wuhan and parts of Omicron or Delta ..\r",{"entities":[[36,46,"ACT"],[71,73,"GPE"],[88,94,"GPE"],[100,107,"ACT"],[147,153,"ACT"]]}],["  REPORT : Elon Musk becomes the SOLE DIRECTOR OF TWITTER – Dissolves the board of directors – ' Plans to fire 25 % ' of staff ..\r",{"entities":[[11,20,"PERSON"],[21,28,"ACT"],[60,69,"ACT"],[106,110,"ACT"]]}],["  Russia will send up to 500,000 tons of its own grain to the poorest countries , particularly in Africa , free of charge in the next 4 months .\r",{"entities":[[2,8,"GPE_WHO"],[14,18,"ACT"],[98,104,"LOC"]]}],["  UP with a GIRL who is always asking for MONEY Is like being released by KIDNAPPERS\r",{"entities":[[31,37,"ACT"],[62,70,"ACT"]]}],["  by Hankyoreh : Similar moment occurred in same alley THREE HOURS ( 6 - 6.30 pm ) before Itaewon stampede disaster , but the crowd was able to prevent disaster by guidance . Friday , eyewitness said , the crowd similar full like Saturday . Live Update :\r",{"entities":[[5,14,"PERSON"],[32,40,"ACT"],[55,66,"TIME"],[69,80,"TIME"],[90,97,"GPE"],[144,151,"ACT"],[175,181,"DATE"],[195,199,"ACT"],[230,238,"DATE"]]}],["  : 4.3 - magnitude earthquake strikes Goesan in central # SouthKorea – Yonhap\r",{"entities":[[31,38,"ACT"],[39,45,"GPE"],[59,69,"GPE"],[72,78,"ORG"]]}],["  : South Korean President Yoon Suk - yeol spent about 15 minutes at the site of the tragedy in the Itaewon 